<Juliet>, will you hand over[\n]the paperwork there?
<Romeo>, here you go,
Don't you like a man who deliberately[\n]asks you this because he wants to touch[\n]your soft fingers?
......It can't be.[\n]I have no reason to dislike <Romeo>[\n]just because it's you.
Ah, <Juliet>!
<Romeo>!
What if......[\n]If the machine here is just smashed[\n]and destroyed?
Over there~
(Look, how he's talking![\n]In that situation![\n]He's an amazing guy...)
Now, wait![\n]It's dangerous to go now!
I see, you listened to <Manji>[\n]and came to find out a way[\n]to stop Dr. <Riness>'s magic.
Hmm...[\n]What's the relationship with <Manji>?
I don't know much about him.[\n]Just a few times, I've heard[\n]his advice about 「Rubian」.
Ah!
I didn't expect an unawakened 「Rubian」[\n]to appear so suddenly, but I was able[\n]to get a lot of valuable data.
Ah, <Juliet>.[\n]Can I heal your broken heart?
Oh, <Romeo>.[\n]As long as you are by my side[\n]I can overcome anything!
Hey... I need you to focus...[\n]I'll have to settle with <Riness>[\n]but...
Ah... well... Take this.[\n]It's a magic defense item...
That's impossible![\n]You should be here now!
Hey, listen to me.[\n]This is a very dangerous situation!
Oh! Oh, oh, hihihi[\n]It's embarrassing~.
You, there~!
<Juliet>,[\n]I'm so happy to see you smiling.
Yes, with the help[\n]of Alpha Troops...
Wait! <Romeo>![\n]Look at the monitor here!
What's going on, <Juliet>?[\n]You look even more beautiful[\n]when you are embarrassed.
You guys.[\n]No, no way......『Papulatus』...
One minute! <Juliet>!
What do you mean? <Romeo>?[\n]Not awakened?
Huh? Wand?
Yes, I'm sure.[\n]It has not awakened, but...
Unbelievable! Suddenly,[\n]there are two 「Rubian」!
Hwaaaa!!!
......Eeehhh!!
Wait,[\n]it's forbidden to enter.
I'm sorry, but I'll hear about you later.
But it's a bit tricky... What to do...
So, let me come this way.
<Romeo>Please! Be careful!!
<Juliet>To not see you in the blink of an eye is a pain to die.
(...... These people, I don't feel nervous......)
Come on, are you hurt? ......
...... <Romeo>He's already wanted to see it, isn't he?
<Romeo>!
Ah, <Juliet>!
You're safe too!
With the resources here and the books in the {Grand Library}, <Papulatus>you'll surely find a way to fight back.
Yes.
You and I will be the standard-bearers of peace. Just thinking about it is like a dream. <Juliet>!
<Romeo>!
Both are 「Rubian」.
<Juliet>, Let's hurry. You have to East Sea to {Grand Library}.
{Grand Library}?
Dr. <Riness> hasn't given up yet.[\n]He's still looking[\n]for another 「Rubian」...
「Rubian」is dangerous if handled[\n]prematurely. We experienced it.
You'll be able to defend[\n]<Riness>'s magic.
(This would block <Riness>'s magic.)
I'm sure because his data remains.
Obtained the 「Special Earplugs」.
Oh... Are you from {El Nath}?
Whoa!! What... What the heck?
Huh~!
......What... What the heck... Unbelievable...
What does that expression mean?
Huh...? What... What's wrong?
This response is similar, but...[\n]It is not awakened yet.
That magician's wand...
And that warrior...
Huh... In my pocket...?
Now, wait.
But, is 「Rubian」a manastone[\n]that has God's power?
From what I can see,[\n]it's probably in your pocket.
Yes. Right.
Let me briefly explain 「Rubian」.
「Rubian」is a manastone with tremendous[\n]power created by the goddess.
This is what I found out a while ago. 「Rubian」Has at least 4 in the world.
We found out through long-term research[\n]that it is a matter related to[\n]time and space.
Perhaps the portals that exist[\n]in the present world were also made[\n]by the power of 「Rubian」.
Two of them belong to you,[\n]one of them is maintaining[\n]the portals of this world.
And the other one......
......[\n]I was in this lab a long time ago.
{Magatia} has been researching[\n]to uncover the secret of 「Rubian」[\n]for many years.
(Here, too... 「Rubian」...)
Maybe...[\n]Is it my father's memento?
But... It was also impossible to crack[\n]the control code created by God.[\n]Perhaps it was human greed.
Then Doctor <Riness> came up[\n]with a new hypothesis.
<Juliet>,[\n]can you tell the rest of story[\n]with your voice?
The next story is so sad...[\n]It's hard to say.
Yes.[\n]<Romeo>, leave it to me.
The research on [Rubian] itself,[\n]which cannot analyze the control code,[\n]has been abandoned and instead...
It was said that by combining[\n]『Pseudo-life』 and 「Rubian」, you can[\n]control the power of 「Rubian」.
Dr. <Pawen>, who was the director of[\n]the institute at the time,[\n]accepted Dr. <Riness>'s proposal[\n]after much consideration.
<Papulatus> was created.
(< waves... Populates >?)
Time went by, but nothing was achieved,[\n]and the research seemed to be stopped.
As a result......
<Juliet>, will you hand over[\n]the paperwork there?
<Romeo>Now, here.
Don't you like a man who deliberately[\n]asks you this because he wants to touch[\n]your soft fingers?
......It can't be.[\n]I have no reason to dislike <Romeo>[\n]just because it's you.
Ah, <Juliet>!
<Romeo>!
What if......[\n]If the machine here is just smashed[\n]and destroyed?
Over there~
......Oh!
It's always a sad story to hear.[\n]I feel sorry for <Papulatus>.
<Romeo>, calm down.
Thank you, <Juliet>.[\n]After all, only you can comfort me.[\n]Sigh~
Sigh... Oh~ Oh~ Oh...[\n]I've come to look ugly.
So let's hear to the reasons[\n]why you came here?
I'll return this. Thank you[\n]for lending me a valuable item.
I got a call from <Sgt. Izzie>!
...[\n]After all, did they fix their leg...
I get it![\n]Immediately switch to defensive mode.[\n]Close all outer wall gates!
Well, then I'm in trouble![\n]I have to go back!!
Didn't you hear that?[\n]Now the Toy Corps of <Papulatus>[\n]are advancing.
But...
Don't think about anything else.[\n]This is the safest place right now.
(No...[\n]I have to bring <Hatch> from <Rinnes>)
Hey, wherever you go![\n]That route already has toys coming!
I have to go back.[\n]I'll try my best...[\n]Don't worry.
If I could be a strength, I would help too.
Since they have come this far, the first thing to do is to prepare for the withdrawal.
But now you have to go!
I got a call from <Sgt. Izzie>!
...[\n]After all, did they fix their leg...
Found! Accommodate the agents, to close the gates!
Well, then I'm in trouble![\n]I have to go back!!
Didn't you hear that?[\n]Now the Toy Corps of <Papulatus>[\n]are advancing.
But...
Don't think about anything else.[\n]This is the safest place right now.
......
Hey. Wherever you go! The route is already coming from enemies!
I have to go back.[\n]I'll try my best...[\n]Don't worry.
(...... <Papulatus>The person who created <Pawen>the <Riness>.)
(A similar creature synthesized with 「Rubian」...)
(By the way...... <Papulatus>Why did he suddenly move the Toy Legion?)
<Juliet>,[\n]I'm so happy to see you smiling.
Oh! Oh, oh, hihihi[\n]It's embarrassing~.
You, there~!
Oh... Are you from {El Nath}?
Yes, with the help[\n]of Alpha Troops...
Huh~!
Whoa!! What... What the heck?
Wait! <Romeo>![\n]Look at the monitor here!
What's going on, <Juliet>?[\n]You look even more beautiful[\n]when you are embarrassed.
......What... What the heck... Unbelievable...
You guys.[\n]No, no way......『Papulatus』...
Huh...? What... What's wrong?
What does that expression mean?
One minute! <Juliet>!
This response is similar, but...[\n]It is not awakened yet.
What do you mean? <Romeo>?[\n]Not awakened?
That magician's wand...
Huh? Wand?
And that warrior...
From what I can see,[\n]it's probably in your pocket.
Huh... In my pocket...?
Maybe...[\n]Is it my father's memento?
Yes, I'm sure.[\n]It has not awakened, but...
Both are 「Rubian」.
......Eeehhh!!
Hwaaaa!!!
Unbelievable! Suddenly,[\n]there are two 「Rubian」!
Now, wait.
But, is 「Rubian」a manastone[\n]that has God's power?
Yes. Right.
Let me briefly explain 「Rubian」.
「Rubian」is a manastone with tremendous[\n]power created by the goddess.
We found out through long-term research[\n]that it is a matter related to[\n]time and space.
Perhaps the portals that exist[\n]in the present world were also made[\n]by the power of 「Rubian」.
I found out this a while ago,[\n]there are at least 4 「Rubian」[\n]in this world.
Two of them belong to you,[\n]one of them is maintaining[\n]the portals of this world.
And the other one......
......[\n]I was in this lab a long time ago.
<Juliet>,[\n]can you tell the rest of story[\n]with your voice?
The next story is so sad...[\n]It's hard to say.
Yes.[\n]<Romeo>, leave it to me.
{Magatia} has been researching[\n]to uncover the secret of 「Rubian」[\n]for many years.
But... It was also impossible to crack[\n]the control code created by God.[\n]Perhaps it was human greed.
Time went by, but nothing was achieved,[\n]and the research seemed to be stopped.
Then Doctor <Riness> came up[\n]with a new hypothesis.
(...... Doctor <Riness>?)
The research on [Rubian] itself,[\n]which cannot analyze the control code,[\n]has been abandoned and instead...
It was said that by combining[\n]『Pseudo-life』 and 「Rubian」, you can[\n]control the power of 「Rubian」.
Dr. <Pawen>, who was the director of[\n]the institute at the time,[\n]accepted Dr. <Riness>'s proposal[\n]after much consideration.
As a result......
<Papulatus> was created.
......
It's always a sad story to hear.[\n]I feel sorry for <Papulatus>.
<Romeo>, calm down.
Thank you, <Juliet>.[\n]After all, only you can comfort me.[\n]Sigh~
Sigh... Oh~ Oh~ Oh...[\n]I've come to look ugly.
So let's hear to the reasons[\n]why you came here?
......Oh!
<Romeo>.[\n]You always make me happy.
<Romeo>.[\n]You always make me happy.
I mean, as I said earlier...
Is it gone...
It would be nice to be able to go back safely...
The reason why there is a portal anomaly right now is because there is a problem with 「Rubian」.
(<Riness> Doctor? Is the name I heard somewhere...)
Right! Apparently in {Dead Mine} Mr. \[name:S_PC\] <Riness>had been hired by a man named him...
(When I was doing it, I was just making toys... What happened in the meantime?)
(<Papulatus>......)
I got a .DNA sample., but... It cannot be analyzed with the data here.
I think if it was {the great Grand Library}, there would definitely be.
I see. <Romeo>I'm going wherever you go.
Thank you. <Juliet>.
That... Over there... I'm sorry to say...
I didn't have the time before...
Oh! This is not the time. Sure thing... Let's hurry.
Eh... I joined in the middle...
Eh... I joined in the middle...
Well, that item must be 『equipped』[\n]to be useful, so keep that in mind.
Well, thank you!
He is said that the Toy Corps[\n]of <Papulatus> repaired their legs[\n]and are advancing again!
He is said that the Toy Corps[\n]of <Papulatus> repaired their legs[\n]and are advancing again!
