I'm sorry, but the portal to {Perion} is broken, as you can see.
No, this is weird! I want to be clear. I don't know who to talk to!
Anyway, you have to go wherever you go.
Come to think of it, you are[\n]a magician from {Ellinia}, right?
Huh? ......Yes...[\n]Well, but...
Why are you so nervous...[\n]Anyway, did the portals become strange?
Yes, some of them are broken,[\n]some have strange connection.
I heard the anomaly of the goddess's[\n]{Clock Tower} is the cause,[\n]but what does it have to do with it?
The goddess's {Clock Tower} is the axis[\n]of time created by the goddess[\n]when only chaos existed in the world.
I've never heard of such a legend.
That's not just a legend. When 『Time』[\n]is set, 『Distance』 is decided,[\n]when 『Distance』 is decided, 『Space』...
What are you talking about...[\n]Talk a little easier to understand!
In other words, the world we live in[\n]has been bound by time.[\n]When the {Clock Tower} breaks down,[\n]the world itself is twisted.
Aha... So there are the portals.
Portal is a way to move through space,[\n]if the underlying world is twisted[\n]so the portal does...
Did you imagine that?!
Come to think of it, you are[\n]a magician from {Ellinia}, right?
Huh? ......Yes...[\n]Well, but...
Why is it so unsettling...
Yes, some of them are broken,[\n]some have strange connection.
I heard the anomaly of the goddess's[\n]{Clock Tower} is the cause,[\n]but what does it have to do with it?
Yes, I mean... I'm not sure[\n]there's anything wrong with[\n]the goddess's {Clock Tower} yet, but...
I've never heard of such a legend.
That's not just a legend. When 『Time』[\n]is set, 『Distance』 is decided,[\n]when 『Distance』 is decided, 『Space』...
What are you talking about...[\n]Talk a little easier to understand!
In other words, the world we live in[\n]has been bound by time.[\n]When the {Clock Tower} breaks down,[\n]the world itself is twisted.
Aha... So there are the portals.
Portal is a way to move through space,[\n]if the underlying world is twisted[\n]so the portal does...
Did you imagine that?!
Portals aren't normal here and there these days, are they?
The goddess's {Clock Tower} is the axis[\n]of time created by the goddess[\n]when only chaos existed in the world.
......Well, that's just my imagination.
...Hmm?[\n]Oh, you are \[name:R_PC\]~
Are you going to meet your partner?[\n]Ah~ It seems like a lot of work~[\n]
Who has a 「Report」? No, I didn't see it~
That's it. I think it would be a good idea to look inside the village of {Kerning City}~
The ban on using the portal here[\n]has just been lifted~[\n]There is a magician girl[\n]who was with \[name:R_PC\] before.
By the way...\[name:R_PC\]The army wants to go is {Perion}, right?
On this side, it looks like there is a portal leading to {Henesys} or {Ellinia}~
Well, it doesn't really matter to me, but for now, it is.
Ah, this is a {Construction Site}~[\n]It's a bit dangerous to walk around~
I see. So it won't be useless to go this way.
Whoa, the magician of {Ellinia}[\n]that \[name:R_PC\] was talking about.
Oh yes...[\n]{Ellinia} had an airfield...[\n]I remember~
The ban on using the portal here[\n]has just been lifted~[\n]We can finally go to {Ellinia}~[\n]We don't have much to go, but...
If you use the portal on the left,[\n]you can go to {Kerning City},[\n]Go down to {Henesys} or {Ellinia}~
Yes, I mean... I'm not sure[\n]there's anything wrong with[\n]the goddess's {Clock Tower} yet, but...
......Well, that's just my imagination.
So, you're from {Ellinia},[\n]and I'm wondering if there's any other[\n]rumor coming from {Ossyria continent}.
It's okay to jump in moderation, but[\n]coming up might be a bit troublesome~
Is this the magician from {Ellinia}[\n]you were talking about?
Oh, yes. {Ellinia} had an airfield.[\n]I remember~
So, you're from {Ellinia},[\n]and I'm wondering if there's any other[\n]rumor coming from {Ossyria continent}.
And this place is no longer connected with {Perion}~
Huh? Boy? It's true... Anyway, thanks to that guy, the stability of the portal has been confirmed.
If so, this is useless to have you go. There's no portal that leads up there~
Oh, yes... Did you say that the portal on this side of {Perion} is gone...
(Yes. <Maurice> If you're an uncle, you might know about the {Perion} portal...)
Huh? Wondering why it's called?
Sound!
<Maurice> Uncle?
Huh? Are you ever lost and wandering?
Huh? Coming from {Dead Mine}? I don't know where it is, right?
Originally, if you took the portal on the left, it was {Kerning City}... Don't know what's going on?
The ban on using the portal here[\n]has just been lifted~[\n]There was a magician girl[\n]with \[name:R_PC\] before, right?
Huh? Boy? It's true... Anyway, thanks to that guy, the stability of the portal has been confirmed.
However, there are rumors that a portal in the {Perion} direction has been found inside the {Subway}.
I think it would be a good idea to go there once~
