[\t]IGO~ That's what happened!
......Ugh......
[\t]Mr. Gang, are you okay?
[\t]Ha, Grandma...... Over there... I mean... Anyway, I'm not a monk, I'm a person.
[\t]It's the first face I see...??
[\t]Yes, I mean, I'm from somewhere else. Obviously it was {Magatia} a while ago...
[\t].Malawi.?  Where does Mark get in? I don't understand a single thing about it.
[\t]I don't know if it's the {Grand Library}, but the entrance to the Grand Library is on the left side of town.
[\t]Oh yes, thank you! I'm twenty-one!!
[\t]Is that really okay? A child who is neither body nor holy is in a hurry with his mind.
[\t]Hey, that's fine!! I have something to see, and I have to go fast!!
Uh...Ugh...[\n]...Oh, my.
Kyaaa!
(Oh, my...[\n]I feel like I've been falling a lot[\n]lately...)
Oh, I heard there was a person who[\n]suddenly appeared with a 'Bang'...[\n] [\n]This time, it falls from the sky[\n]with a 'Bang'.
Oh, my...[\n]What are you talking about?
Huh? Ah![\n]Hey, you are talking!
......Huh, it's natural to talk[\n]because I'm a human!
Ah, excuse me......
From the standpoint of an objective[\n]observer...
By the way, is there a person[\n]who appeared with a 'Bang'?
Yes. Not long ago,[\n]my Grandma told me that a person[\n]appeared also with a 'Bang'.
(The person who appeared with[\n]a 'Bang'... Who is it?)
So, where is that person?
In the {Grand Library}, reading books.[\n]Maybe...
Words are too hard!
......Anyway, it was {Grand Library},[\n]right? Thanks.
{Grand Library}, the portal on the left[\n]side of the town.
You fell from the sky, are you okay?[\n]Is the law of gravity being ignored?
...
{Grand Library}? You can go through[\n]the book on the left side of town.
Hmm... Song... I think I've heard of that[\n]somewhere...
A song that has been passed down?
[\t]If it's a {Grand Library}, it's on the left side of town. I just told you, have you forgotten about it already?
Oh, it's you.[\n]Did you finish your business?
[\t]There are books floating on the portal, so anyone can recognize them at a glance.
[\t]Ok. That's great. Huh? And going back? Already?
[\t]Nowadays, a lot of people come to see it for the first time.
[\t]I see a lot of faces that I haven't seen lately.
Huh?[\n]Did you get the 「Goblin’s Song」?[\n]Really??
You are a kid who fell from the sky.[\n]A similar thing happened a while ago.
So...[\n]Are you done with your business now?
Ahem... Hem...[\n]Are you came from under the well?
Ahem... Hem...[\n]You can go to another world[\n]through {Grand Library}.
Under the well?
Huh? It's the first time I've seen you.[\n]Did you come here after passing[\n]the {Grand Library}?
Yes, if you go into the book[\n]on the left side of town,[\n]you can go to the {Grand Library}.
Heiya~~[\n]There's nothing to envy in the world.
Heiya~ The mountain behind the town[\n]is called {Black Mountain}.[\n]Hehe~ Heiya~
Huh?[\n]Did you really defeat the goblin?
She suddenly appeared in the middle[\n]with a 'Bang'.
[\t]Work... Grandmother. Where's this?
(......It's a little strange[\n]how she's surprised.)
Nobody believed it.
Honey. That's in the direction of[\n]{Black Mountain}.[\n]You shouldn't go there.
There are scary ghosts[\n]in {Black Mountain}, so it's not a place[\n]for kids to go.
Honey. That's in the direction of[\n]{Black Mountain}.[\n]You shouldn't go there.
But, I have to climb {Black Mountain}.
You are a kid who knows the value of[\n]promises and is even brave.
However, it would be nice to hear about[\n]the legend of {Black Mountain}.
I want to find a song.
Yes, there is a scary ghost[\n]in {Black Mountain}.
Okay. You'd like to hear my story.[\n]Then I'll tell you.
Yes, is there anything else you would[\n]like to know?
What is the legend of {Black Mountain}?
How do I defeat the ghosts?
No, maybe next time.
Ok. This is how to defeat the ghosts.
Grandma, I've been there~!
Oh... Did you get back safely?[\n]So, what happened?
I finished the 「Goblin’s Song」.
That's great. That's really great.[\n]I was worried...
Anyway, the ghosts won't appear[\n]in {Black Mountain} anymore.[\n]
Yes.[\n]Everyone in the town will be happy.[\n]That's great.
In the past, there was a way under[\n]the well so you could go to the sea.[\n]
Your outfit was unusual, so I thought[\n]you were from the sea. Isn't it?[\n]
{Grand Library}?
Ahem.. A song that is passed down[\n]to the town? Is it the 「Goblin’s Song」?[\n]
One day, God sent a goblin to[\n]{Black Mountain} to hide a song.
Ahem... Ahem...
The goblin divided the song into[\n]several and hid it in {Black Mountain}[\n]and had ghosts guard it.
There is a legend like that,[\n]but isn't it just a legend?[\n]Ahem...
It's just what kids say.[\n]It doesn't make sense to go [\n]into such a strange thing.
The {Grand Library} seems to have led[\n]to a different world...[\n]It was a world I had never seen before.
After all,[\n]you're a strong "super-ego" type.[\n]We will be happy thanks to you.
A long time ago, God sent down[\n]a goblin to {Black Mountain}.
With a mission of guarding the song[\n]carved on the sacred Song Tree.
The goblin divided the song into 3,[\n]so that people could not find it,[\n]and made 2 more fake songs and hid it[\n]all over {Black Mountain}.
Correct.[\n]
Listen to the elders. You'll have[\n]nothing to lose by listening.
A kid who appeared a while ago?
Yes, she's probably[\n]in the {Grand Library} right now.
Yes, Grandma.
Then you'll go somewhere else again.
As expected... You have to walk around[\n]a lot when you're young. If you're old,[\n]you can't go even if you want to.
As the saying goes,[\n]"There is a way in a book".[\n]Is there really a way in a book?[\n]
Since earlier, "id" and "ego",[\n]and what is that![\n]I hate complicated things!
The gravitational force acting between[\n]two objects is in the direction of the[\n]straight line connecting two objects,
Law of gravity???
Stop it!!!
With the kid who appeared a while ago,[\n]I still had some words...
Heiya~~[\n]Who in the world is happier than me?
Huh?[\n]Are you from another town?
Welcome to this place.[\n]But, it doesn't have anything special.
Even if you close your eyes and stay[\n]still in the sun,[\n]there is nothing to envy in the world.
There are many ghosts in {Black[\n]Mountain}. Hehe~ Heiya~[\n]You need a song to chase away ghosts~
Heiya~ The song is engraved[\n]on a sacred tree~[\n]Check the tree and sing a song~
This guy... He's crazy about singing.
Really?
Wow~~[\n]You were such a great kid.
I can now go to {Black Mountain}.[\n]Thank you.
Each ghost is guarding an old tree.
Really?[\n]Are you really defeated the goblin[\n]and completed the song?
Ah?[\n]I can't go,[\n]what do you mean?
[\t]...
[\t]Anyway, you'll have nothing to lose[\n]by listening to the elders,[\n]don't think about going.
It's still waiting for the song.
And each song was told to guard by[\n]the ghosts that roams in the Heaven.
Ah? So 2 of them are fake.
However, in {Black Mountain} there is[\n]a sacred tree called Song Tree,[\n]which remembers its original song.
But, if you sing song of an old tree[\n]guarded by a ghost,
Their souls cannot go far[\n]because they are bound by songs carved[\n]on old trees.
Naturally, the connection between[\n]the song and the soul will be broken[\n]and they will ascend to heaven.
If it's {Black Mountain}, you can follow[\n]the path on the top right of this town,[\n]where ghosts come out.
[\t]Maybe she's coming to this world and[\n]thinking that the balance between "ego"[\n]and "id" has collapsed and she is[\n] looking for a replacement for[\n]"super-ego"?
It's a social shift,[\n]the ego can't follow.
[\t]Are there ghosts in {Black Mountain}?
I've once passed the {Grand Library}[\n]and went to the top of the tower.
A city called {Ludibrium} came out...[\n]There were people who looked completely[\n]different from us.
But one day the elevator didn't work,[\n]so I haven't been there since then.
What do you do with {Black Mountain}?
If it's a song... Are you going to[\n]find the 「Goblin’s Song」?
The song is guarded[\n]by ghosts.
I made a promise with my friend.[\n]And I'm not afraid of ghosts.
[\t]Earlier, a boy had fallen from the sky.
[\t]Where are you going? The {Grand Library} is on the left side of town~
[\t]If you go out there, it's in the direction of {Black Mountain}. I like that the Sunni ghost doesn't come out and go.
[\t]In fact, now is not the time to do this. I need to find the secret of molecular formula in {Grand Library}.
[\t]Where are you going? The {Grand Library} is on the left side of town~
[\t]Oh... I've seen everything I see in the {Grand Library}. I was a little curious to see what was going on here...
[\t]Ok? If you want to go, you might want to go.
[\t]Even so, it's a rugged mountain, so it's not a good place.
[\t]Yes~ Thanks for letting me know.
[\t](Is a brave young man \[name:S_PC\]...)
[\t]Mr. <Romeo>, Mrs. <Juliet>, I'll save you.
[\t]!!!
[\t]Ugh......
[\t]What... What the heck... What happened?
[\t]<... Mr. Romeo >!
[\t]<Juliet>Seed!
[\t]......Is it a person????
[\t]What the heck happened?
[\t]Does he look a lot like our hands?
[\t]That... But where is Grandma here?
[\t]This is the {Folk Town}.
[\t]{Folk Town}...?
[\t](Where did you hear about it?)
[\t](That's right! Apparently <Romeo>Mr. {The Grand Library} is between the {Helios Tower} and the {Folk Town}.)
[\t](But how did you get here?)
[\t](Uh? Could it be that this 「Rubian」Protected me?)
[\t]Grandmother!
[\t]Huh? What's wrong?
[\t]Is there a {Grand Library} near here?
{Grand Library}?
[\t]I have one more win!
[\t]!?
[\t]Not Marathi, but {Magatia}.
[\t](Anyway, that's not the point right now.)
[\t]Ugh... Ugh...
[\t]I've once passed the {Grand Library} and taken the elevator up to the top of the tower.
A city called {Ludibrium} came out...[\n]There were people who looked completely[\n]different from us.
[\t]But one day the elevator didn't work, so I haven't been there since.
Heiya~~[\n]There's nothing to envy in the world.
Heiya~~[\n]Who in the world is happier than me?
Huh?[\n]Are you from another town?
[\t]Came here well. Nothing special to see but[\n]
[\t]Even if you close your eyes and stay still in the sun, there is nothing to envy in the world.[\n]
[\t]In the old days, there was a path under a well so that you could go to the sea...
[\t]Somehow, one day the well was blocked.
{Grand Library}? You can go through[\n]the book on the left side of town.
[\t]Is there really a way in a book, as in saying .There is a way in a book.?
[\t]Has something happened to my town?
[\t]Finally, a little while ago, a brave young man eradicated all the ghosts that live in the mountains, so it will be fine.
[\t]He, just, I was wondering where this is.
[\t]I had passed by a warrior child earlier...
[\t]That's a bit of a pity. I would have been a good friend with Wool Son... Oh... Ok. Right.
When a ghost is attached, it will[\n]absorb life force in an instant.[\n]
[\t]That's why, {Black Mountain} cannot be[\n]entered by anyone.
[\t]Heiya~~[\n]There's nothing to envy in the world.
[\t](And because {Helios Tower} is the pillar that supports {Ludibrium})
[\t](You could go to {Ludibrium} through {Grand Library}.)
The legend of {Black Mountain}?
I'll hear about it next time.
This is very important.[\n]You must hear it. Are you sure[\n]didn't want to hear it?
Yes, I'd love to hear it.
No, I don't want to hear it now.
If the ghost is attached, don't panic,[\n]you can quickly remove it[\n]by pressing any button repeatedly. 
And the ghosts don't fall,[\n]once they are ascended.
Ok. This is how to defeat the ghosts.
Each ghost is guarding an old tree.
Their souls cannot go far[\n]because they are bound by songs carved[\n]on old trees.
But, if you sing song of an old tree[\n]guarded by a ghost,
Naturally, the connection between[\n]the song and the soul will be broken[\n]and they will ascend to heaven.
And the ghosts don't fall,[\n]once they are ascended.
If the ghost is attached, don't panic,[\n]you can quickly remove it[\n]by pressing any button repeatedly. 
Honey. You need to listen how to defeat[\n]the ghosts first.
Huh? How to defeat the ghosts?
Yes, thank you.
Its size is proportional to the product[\n]of the masses of the two objects...
Yes, that's right! I've heard that[\n]there is a legend about song[\n]in {Black Mountain}.
Huh?[\n]Where is {Black Mountain}?
[\t]It's summer if it's a little bit. Be sure to come then. This half will pick a delicious watermelon.
