Above~
Huh?
It would be better not to go to the mountains.
What's going on in the mountains?
It's still cold and bittersweet. It's the first time the temperature has dropped like this during this time.
Anyone from {Ludibrium}? You're the only TAJ I've seen here.
That's right, there are people who go to the mountains and don't come back. There are already five of them.
They're all friends who are used to the mountains.
Thanks for helping a friend.
Thank you so much earlier. <Yeti>There's still a lot of left? What the heck is going on?
Wizard brother!!  Did you meet again!? Thank you so much!  Have you seen animals that are white and black?
How to get help and show your gratitude. Will others be safe?
!!!
These are toys???
Whoa
!!!
Uncle alone... Did you survive?
......
Wool... Beats me. Suddenly, the toy guys came in.
From then on I'll explain.
!!!
I thought I had caught all the moving toys, but I still had them.
I chase these guys and call them Sgt.  from the {Omega Sector}.
We arrived at this village where the same phenomenon as {Ludibrium} is happening.
When I came, the villagers had already been hit by toys.
As a result of gathering information from Alpha troopers from all over the country, they seem to be heading to {Magatia}.
...... {Magatia}?
{Magatia} has the world's largest research institute.
Perhaps, something is going to be there. Otherwise, there would be no reason for the toys to head there.
I have to find out about the ecology and purpose of toys in {Magatia}.
{Magatia}......
What's going on in the mountains...
I heard the news. You said you saved someone who was trapped in the ice.
Oh, you saved all the villagers. Thank you so much. Thanks.
Ah, Thanks a lot for being able to get out.
(Are people disappearing here too? What does it have to do with the {Ludibrium} incident?)
(Shall we find out more about what's going on?)
You. Haven't you heard the advice of this old man? The mountains are dangerous.
......I don't want to go too far, but...
Whether it's because of the sudden arrival of the Korean wave these days, the villagers who went out into the mountains are not returning.
But I have to investigate the upheaval in this vicinity.
Can you reiterate what you said earlier?
Oh, oh, did you save the villagers who were trapped in the mountains? Thank you. Thanks.
Oh, oh, did you save the villagers who were trapped in the mountains? Thank you. Thanks.
However, there are still 4 of them in the mountains. It's an unsolicited request, but can you save others?
However, there are still 3 of them in the mountains. It's an unsolicited request, but can you save others?
Oh, oh, did you save the villagers who were trapped in the mountains? Thank you. Thanks.
However, there are still 2 people in the mountains. It's an unsolicited request, but can you save others?
Oh, oh, did you save the villagers who were trapped in the mountains? Thank you. Thanks.
However, 1 person is still in the mountains. It's an unsolicited request, but can you save him?
I have acquired the 「Tornado I」 Skill.
Nope. Don't say such humble words. Thanks to that, everyone was safe. I'll accept this.
It is a gift of gratitude to you on behalf of the villagers.
I'm glad everyone is unharmed. It's all thanks to you.
Whether it's because of the sudden arrival of the Korean wave these days, the villagers who went out into the mountains are not returning.
So, don't go to the mountains for the time being.
Ah, I appreciate it.
I just found people on the way. It wasn't a very difficult task.
Is it here for some reason? I've been stuck at home for a long time. So I came to see the chapter like a mother.
By the way... In this town, there are not many people. Where did everyone go?
{Ludibrium} Villager? No, I've never seen it...
Elder {Ellinia} asked me to investigate the events in this vicinity...
Elder {Ellinia}? Did He send you?
Indeed, heaven has not abandoned us. If Elder {Ellinia} sent you, you can trust him.
I would appreciate it if you could investigate the whereabouts of the villagers. There are currently 5 people who are missing.
So don't climb the mountain for the time being.
You. Haven't you heard the advice of this old man? The mountains are dangerous.
......I don't want to go too far, but...[\n]
Elder {Ellinia} asked me to investigate the events in this vicinity...
Elder {Ellinia}? Did He send you?
Indeed, heaven has not abandoned us. If Elder {Ellinia} sent you, you can trust him.
I would appreciate it if you could investigate the whereabouts of the villagers. There are currently 5 people who are missing.
Elder {Ellinia} sent you, of course, you will be very good,
{El Nath} is a rough road. In particular, you have to be careful of icicles falling all over the place.
Yay,~ It's a village!
If my guess is correct, there will definitely be {Ludibrium} people here.
What... What the heck...?
There are so many Wen toys in town, right?
The villagers are down!
Radish... What's up?
Well, what is this guy! Save me!!
Shriek!
Pooh!
Toys that look stronger! <Did Sgt. > Charlie and his uncle evacuate safely?
Where? Is it not an inn?
Ok. I've seen it in books. It was a city of magic and science, right?
I thought I would have to hide for a while...
What is the purpose of the toys? Why are you raiding the village?
Weird toys and award-winning labs. Don't you think something is involved?
Huh... Elder? Elder!!!
It's like this...
It doesn't seem like the purpose is to specifically raid people.
Oh!
It's scary, but... You can't just listen to the screams and pass by.
You go with it too.
Behind him, he follows.
Two... Oh, dear... I'm not breathing.
Hey! Hey!!!
Hey! Hey!!! Get up!
Wool... All... What happened?
It's the first time I've had such a terrible cold. What's happened these days?
I'll have to see what happened to the village.
