First, if you're on this rock, you'll be safe!
Ok!! As much as possible, the attention of the enemy is directed towards us!
Sure thing! Let's go!!
First go back to town! A few are still chasing after you! Let me buy time!
Ha, but!!
You're taking the wounded with you, right? Don't worry, I'll get away no matter what!!
First, if you're on this rock, you'll be safe!
Ok!! As much as possible, the attention of the enemy is directed towards us!
Sure thing! Let's go!!
\[name:R_PC\] became a companion.
The Archer became a companion.
Ugh... I'm sorry. Because of me.
