Igogogo...... It just keeps falling.
By the way, where else is this? ...... Is it a nice scenery somehow?
Sorry though. I'm cancelling now.
There is a surge of monsters on the route, so the safety of the passengers cannot be guaranteed.
Oh my gosh, did you go out into the outside world and then come back?
Anyway, looking at your level, I'll have to practice here for the time being.
It's been a long time, remember me~?
The anomaly in the portal are preventing new adventurers from coming. The guide work is also closed for a while.
Even if you take a quiz, the adventurers won't come...
I'm a helper to help beginners level up.
If you go out <Snail>of town, I'll <Snail>grab a house and collect the 「Shell」 and I'll reward you.
......Ugh... Ugh...
You can collect the 「Snail Shell」 and the .9..
I still don't have enough 「Snail Shell」. I need to collect 9 dogs. Cheer up.
That's over 5. Half way through. Cheer up. Now, and this is a gift.
Somehow it reminds me of the old days. Purely enjoyed cultivation...
You've collected all 9! So, let me give you a gift.
Right. And I've heard this or that.
That is right. However, you can't always live in the pursuit of strength.
The important thing is not to forget that it was fun alone.
The world is fun in itself, but when you grow up, you forget about it.
Hey... One minute...
You, apparently, have you fallen from the sky? There is another person who has just fallen from heaven like you.
It was at the far right of town... How about going there? Maybe you know?
What's so fidgeting? Why don't you just live comfortably here?
Now, wait! You!
(Huh? Where did I see it?...)
Ugh! Fireball!
You're not trying to attack me now, right?
Oh, ah, sorry. I thought it was a monster at the moment...
Did you see my face so beautiful and mistake it for a monster? ...... Has the courage, you?
Ooh, ha I'm scared! He was a monster too!
Par, Fireball.....
If I just talk to you, I hear that there is no progress, right?
Huh?  How do you know that?
I knew that!
......Anyway, that's it. By the way, where the heck did you fly from?
Ah, that's it, I boarded a Ship bound for {Ludibrium}...
Suddenly, monsters appeared and fell off the Ship.
......
From there, I wandered around and entered a strange portal... This time it's here.
............Hmm. Same as me.
Why? Listening to me, I suddenly felt disappointed...
No, no. It's not your fault.
I'm actually looking for a way out of here, but I'm not making any progress at all.
I thought if you flew outside, you knew how to get out. ...... After all, you were an accident.
Not really... Wouldn't there be a path somewhere?
I have a place to go... What if?... What if?
Okay, you look like a Magician, but give me some cooperation. The two of you are looking for a way to get outside.
Yes, yep!! Hugh... Lived.
What else is suddenly reassuring! You have to help! Leaving it all to me!?
Now, wait! You!
......
Ugh! Fireball!
You're not trying to attack me now, right?
Oh, ah, sorry. I thought it was a monster at the moment...
Did you see my face so beautiful and mistake it for a monster? ...... Has the courage, you?
Ooh, ha I'm scared! He was a monster too!
Par, Fireball.....
If I just talk to you, I hear that there is no progress, right?
Huh?  How do you know that?
I knew that!
......Anyway, that's it. By the way, where the heck did you fly from?
Ah, that's it, I boarded a Ship bound for {Ludibrium}...
Suddenly, monsters appeared and fell off the Ship.
......
From there, I wandered around and entered a strange portal... This time it's here.
............Hmm. Same as me.
Why? Listening to me, I suddenly felt disappointed...
No, no. It's not your fault.
I'm actually looking for a way out of here, but I'm not making any progress at all.
I thought if you flew outside, you knew how to get out. ...... After all, you were an accident.
Not really... Wouldn't there be a path somewhere?
I have a place to go... What if?... What if?
Okay, you're like a Magician, please give me some cooperation. The two of you are looking for a way to get outside.
Yes, yep!! Hugh... Lived.
What else is suddenly reassuring! You have to help! Leaving it all to me!?
Oh my gosh, is this a child's friend?
I'm a helper to help beginners level up.
Oh boy? By the way... You seem to have already reached the level of cultivation here.
Perhaps you are here for sightseeing purposes? Also, the nature of {Maple Island} here is beautiful, isn't it?
Yes... That is right. I'm the captain driving a Ship to {Lith Port}<Shanks>.
There is a surge of monsters on the route, so we can't guarantee the safety of our passengers.
That's why... There is no guarantee of when the Ship will be able to depart again.
Hello. Captain of the Gloria<Shanks>. What's going on?
It's been a long time. Remember me?
Anyway... No new adventurers are coming these days. So the guide work is also closed for a while.
I've heard that the portal connecting {Leth Port} and {Henesys} has disappeared, and that's probably why, right?
Huh? Is it a little bit more real? Does your look improve?
You... What's so fidgeting? If you're a beginner, you have to practice hard.
Oh, you~ did you come round the {Maple Island}?
Scenic isn't it? It's quiet and perfect for relaxing after a walk. Isn't it?
But... This way... The downside is that once you jump down, you have to come back from town...
Do you see the wooden sign that looks to my right?
Oh, another one. Besides, I don't know the exit......
This is the will of Heaven. Stop giving up. It's also not too bad to live quietly.
It was such a pleasure to be purely strong...
\[name:M_PC\] became a companion.
\[name:A_PC\] became a companion.
......Let me see...
Have you forgotten it because it's been so long? You practiced here a long time ago. Maybe you came to your brother?
I remember the first time you saw < red snail >, you were so surprised that you ran to the village and cried.
Radish... What are you talking about! When I was amazed at <red snails>!
Ho ho ho... I remember.
(Ignore Everywhere You Go! Ignore! Ignore Me! I'm Treated Like a Beginner!!!)
(That weird woman, I won't forgive you!!!)
Unfortunately, we are now in a cancellation.
Hey.
Sounds like a beginner, would it be a good idea to listen to me and get out?
(What... That guy? ... Cheekily.)
Ah If so, you want to go to {Lith Port}.
However, there is now a surge of monsters on the route, which is taking a break from the operation of the ferry.
We'll take care of all the monsters, so go ahead and grab the key.
Hiik~ Do we deal with monsters? I don't want to do that...
(Be quiet! isn't that something you have to leave here somehow?)
......Thank you for the words, but... The guest doesn't look very strong.
And the Magician next to you seems to be scared...
......Also... No, I can't. Please go back.
...I'm not a beginner!
......I don't know your situation yet. If you just think about it, won't you be able to get out of this place for the rest of your life?
Now that I feel like I have become a cultivator, I will give you some useful information.
If you hide behind me, the monster won't recognize you.
You'll be all over {Maple Island}, so it's a good idea to use it if you need to.
Shall I go back to town now?... I was thinking about going for a little more walk.
Huh? Did you ask me to collect the? 「Snail Shell」 Now?
(...... But... If you look at my condition right now, it's not that he is wrong.)
(Until I find that weird girl, I'll first go back to the beginners and level them up.)
You like. 「Snail Shell」 .9., right? I'll get it right away.
I won 2 「Red Potion」.
Obtained the 「Hunter's Bow」.
I gave him the 「Snail Shell」 <Rain>.
How's that? Haven't you climbed the level quite a bit?
???
The number of 「Snail Shell」 to be collected is .9..
Ask me, the best of {Henesys}, to collect the 「Snail Shell」?
But... I think you're a newbie, right?
The combat power seems to be low, and the equipment you have...
(Chet... yes, great. You can't deal with that strange woman in the current state.)
(Actually, the level is lousy with combat power on the floor... The equipment is also for beginners only...)
......Do you have the heart to do it?
The place away was where the aliens were at war.
......?
Oh boy... Oh boy... Of course I'll help too. Don't be angry.
Ok. Come to think of it, you didn't even know our names, did you? I say \[name:A_PC\](this).
Yes... My name is \[name:M_PC\]. I hope I am in your good hands.
You like. So let's go find a way out.
......The world is joyful with that alone.
......
The place away was where the aliens were at war.
Oh boy... Oh boy... Of course I'll help too. Don't be angry.
Ok. Come to think of it, you didn't even know our names, did you? I say \[name:A_PC\](this).
Yes... My name is \[name:M_PC\]. I hope I am in your good hands.
You like. So let's go find a way out.
Oh boy... Hello.
You seem a little useful, right? The greetings are bright... Who does it compare to a bit?
I'm still easily excited.
One minute! You! Are you talking about me?
Anyway, look at your newbie friend and let me know some good information.
Do you see the wooden sign that looks to my right?
If you hide behind me, the monster won't recognize you.
You'll be all over {Maple Island}, so it's a good idea to use it if you need to.
Then go have fun and enjoy.
Oh, you guys – did you come round {Maple Island}?
Isn't that good too? Where is this place? The view is nice, quiet and perfect for relaxing after a walk.
Oh boy? And then it turned out... Have you seen it too?
I once went for a walk to the depths and saw a strange portal.
It was a red portal... I tried to go in, but it disappeared.
If you're interested in the red portal, look for the deepest part of the forest.
Oh yes, my brother <Sen>saw a red portal in the woods that said it had appeared and disappeared.
It was a strange shape, so I just ran away...
Red portal?
!!!
Huh? Interested in red portal? If so<Sen>, ask him directly, probably at the inn.
Oh, another one. By the way... I don't know the exit......
This may be the will of Heaven. What about giving up and living quietly here?
Hello. Captain of the Gloria<Shanks>. What's going on?
Ah If so, you want to go to {Lith Port}.
However, there is now a surge of monsters on the route, which is taking a break from the operation of the ferry.
We'll take care of all the monsters, so go ahead and grab the key.
Hiik~ Do we deal with monsters? I don't want to do that...
(Be quiet! isn't that something you have to leave here somehow?)
......Thank you for the words, but... The guest doesn't look very strong.
And the Magician next to you seems to be scared...
......Also... No, I can't. Please go back.
Oh, and newbie guests have been around for a long time, right?
At the time, I was just practicing running! And who cried, right?
There were a lot of adventurers back then...
Oh yes, my brother <Sen>saw a red portal in the woods that said it had appeared and disappeared.
It was a strange shape, so I just ran away...
!!!
(Nor am I wrong.)
Huh? Interested in red portal? If so<Sen>, ask him directly, probably at the inn.
Is that so?...? You could think of it that way...
Oh my gosh, is this a child's friend?
Oh boy... Hello.
You seem a little useful, right? The greetings are bright... Who does it compare to a bit?
One minute! You! Are you talking about me?
I'm still easily excited.
Anyway, look at your newbie friend and let me know some good information.
Do you see the wooden sign that looks to my right?
If you hide behind me, the monster won't recognize you.
You'll be all over {Maple Island}, so it's a good idea to use it if you need to.
Oh!
Obtained 5000 mesos.
Yat-ho!
Oh?
Yay!
Obtained 5000 mesos.
