Excuse me.
How did you get here?
I was on the {Subway} just now,[\n]and all of a sudden[\n]came out in the mountain...
So where is this?
This is the {Excavation Site} camp[\n]of the {Sharenian} ruins near {Perion}.
{Sharenian} ruins?
What the heck.[\n]I walked a lot,[\n]but after all it's near {Perion}.
In short, you've come here[\n]through the red portal.
Well,[\n]rather than saying "came through",[\n]I was swept away and came here without[\n]even knowing.
It's great to have survived there.
To some extent...
How's that? Won't you work under me?[\n]It's about guarding the excavations.
To do this, I have to get permission[\n]from my Grandpa first...
Yes, I will do my best.
It's okay to start with something[\n]simple.
Wow! Did Grandpa really allow it?
Then, it is decided.
For now, keep an eye for intruders[\n]around the {Excavation Site}.
Yes, got it.
Yes, understood.
This excavation is very important[\n]project. Keep the security tight!
Be careful! \[name:R_PC\]![\n]
And you have to be careful not to hurt[\n]the Maple Agent![\n]
Is it okay?[\n]\[name:R_PC\] didn't bother you, right?[\n]
Be careful! \[name:R_PC\\\]![\n]
Mr. <Riness>.[\n]
What is going on?[\n]
I've brought a man with me who[\n]has business with Mr. <Riness>.[\n]
The place where the wild boar[\n]is on the right side of the tent.[\n]Get rid as soon as possible.[\n]
Mr. <Riness>,[\n]I've been fighting as you wish.
You're really Maple Agent.[\n]So, can you read 「Tablet」 as well?
Okay![\n]Where then... Shall I see it?
Hi... Mr. <Riness>...[\n]I worked hard too...
You're a bodyguard, isn't it obvious?[\n]
......
Mr. <Riness>.[\n]Now, let me read the 「Tablet」.
Well.... I see.
The location of the {Sharenian Palace}[\n]seems to be right at the top[\n]of the mountain in the cyclone.
A cyclone is a defensive spell[\n]to protect the palace.
It seems this 「Tablet」[\n]is simply a record.
Anyway, a promise is a promise,[\n]so I'll give you the information.[\n]
I appreciate it!
Hey, you're out.[\n]I can't tell anyone who is irrelevant.
[\t]Here, I found a red gem that looks like a 「Rubian」.
[\t]So, how did you do that?
[\t]Now, it's not here. <Chrishrama>I gave it to a monk named him.[\n]
[\t]He was a monk of {Slight Temple}. In that temple, the legend of the {Sharenian} has been passed down and kept.
[\t]Huh?  Did you pass on 「Rubian」So easily?
[\t]Well, it was a cursed gem.
[\t]It's not scary. You said it was the temple of {Sleepywood}?
[\t]If the monk wasn't lying, 「Rubian」Would be enshrined in the temple of {Sleepywood}.[\n]
Mr. <Riness>, thank you!![\n]
[\t]How are you? How was it?[\n]
Isn't that a big deal?[\n]
<Chrishrama> of {Sleepywood Temple}.[\n]He must know about 「Rubian」.[\n]
What are you doing? You can't chase[\n]that Maple Agent, can you?!
Don't make me say the same thing twice![\n]I hate stupid people!
Ugh... Ugh.
Oh! Doctor![\n]I think his consciousness has returned.
Uh... what?
It's okay.[\n]There was nothing wrong with your body.
What is this?[\n]...Excavation team camp...
Right.
......The top of the mountain......
You were carried to this place by[\n]a cyclone from top of the mountain.
Well, even if the portals is twisted,[\n]I can do research here,[\n]so it's rather convenient.
I'm finally helping Dr. <Nuris> here.[\n]I don't know how to return to {Perion}.
I ended up working part-time here.[\n]I don't know how to return to {Perion}.
The excavation team has disbanded,[\n]as they told us to take care[\n]the equipment we were using.[\n]We remain and continue to excavate.
I don't have enough staff,[\n]but it's nice to be able to study[\n]more comfortably than before.
Wait, \[name:R_PC\].[\n]You're going to come all the way here[\n]and go back without any harvest?
Now, the man over there is excavation[\n]team leader, <Riness>.
Ah~ A palace where a cyclone blows![\n]It is in such an inconvenient place!
However,[\n]even if you know that the cyclone[\n]is a defensive magic...[\n]There is no way to stop it.
......[\n]Who are you?
On the way to {Henesys}, I rode[\n]the red portal and I came here.
I know you're able to handle a sword.
Oh, there's something I have to do.
Mr. <Riness>...
What is going on?[\n]
I've brought a man with me who[\n]has business with Mr. <Riness>.[\n]
Hello?[\n]
Who are you?
I have something I want to ask.
I'm a busy man.[\n]It's hard to come without[\n]an appointment.[\n]Can you come back?
Hey![\n]Let's take guests to the exit.[\n]
Okay, okay!
What?
I got this from {Excavation Site}.
Hmm?[\n]....Is it a 「Tablet」?[\n]It's like a {Sharenian} artifact.[\n]
......
You what?
Do you know how to read it!?
Wow. That's great! \[name:R_PC\]!![\n]
For some reason, but...[\n]I have little knowledge, you know?
Are you pretending![\n]It's an ancient {Sharenian} text![\n]Where did you learn that!![\n]
Don't you think he is guessing[\n]around in moderation?
No, some of the texts are decrypted.[\n]It's clearly engraved[\n]with "<Sharen VIII>".
(Well......)
It's true.[\n]I don't know why I can read this.[\n]
In fact, he is an orphan and doesn't[\n]remember much from his childhood.[\n]Maybe it's something he learned[\n]when he was a kid.[\n]
Well...
Now, could you read it more closely?
All right, but do us a favor, too.[\n]Please.
Ah, ah, okay...[\n]What do you want?
I'm looking for a gem called 「Rubian」.
「Rubian」......?
「Rubian」... Why are you looking[\n]something like that?
Oh... That's...
We owe it to this guy,[\n]who is a {Sharenian} lover.[\n]He told me to bring[\n]some money or 「Rubian」.
Debt.....?
It's debt.[\n]Woo-hoo, hoo-ha-ha!
Haha haha. Ha ha ha.[\n]Okay, I'll let you know.
Really? Glad to hear that!
But there's one thing I want to ask.
Why don't you listen[\n]to the information after you're done[\n]with it?
Two jobs...[\n]You're trying to sell it at a pretty[\n]high price, aren't you?
I'm sure it's worth it.
I'd rather have faith than[\n]a kind person.[\n]It's okay. Let's do it!
Not long ago, a wild boar have entered[\n]into the {Excavation Site}...[\n]It is interfering the excavation work.
I've thought about going out[\n]and catching it myself,[\n]but I don't know where the den is...
Hey! Bodyguard!
Huh? Me too? Sounds like fun![\n]We'll be back!
So, me too!
You stay. Two is enough.[\n]These days, you're probably a little[\n]dull because you're only in the office.
He is thinking of the lady.[\n]The terrain on {Perion} is quite rough.
<Rina>, please stay.[\n]It's dangerous and...[\n]If you stay, I feel at ease.
Huh?
I'm \[name:R_PC\]. Good luck.
The {Excavation Site} is on the right[\n]side of the tent. So, let's get off[\n]to the right end!
Mr. <Riness>,[\n]I'm back.
Mr. <Riness>,[\n]I've been fighting as you wish.
You're really Maple Agent.[\n]So, can you read 「Tablet」 as well?
Okay![\n]Where then... Shall I see it?
Hi... Mr. <Riness>...[\n]I worked hard too...
You're a bodyguard, isn't it obvious?[\n]
......
Mr. <Riness>.[\n]Now, let me read the 「Tablet」.
Well.... I see.
The location of the {Sharenian Palace}[\n]seems to be right at the top[\n]of the mountain in the cyclone.
Ah~ A palace where a cyclone blows![\n]It is in such an inconvenient place!
A cyclone is a defensive spell[\n]to protect the palace.
However,[\n]even if you know that the cyclone[\n]is a defensive magic...[\n]There is no way to stop it.
It seems this 「Tablet」[\n]is simply a record.[\n]
Anyway, a promise is a promise,[\n]so I'll give you the information.[\n]
I appreciate it!
Hey, you're out.[\n]I can't tell anyone who is irrelevant.
Mr. <Riness>,[\n]I'm back.
What, me!?
You're just the bodyguard I hired.[\n]Get out of here!
......Okay.
(He looks strong on the outside,[\n]but he's a little clumsy,[\n]so please take good care of him.)
The excavation work is getting more[\n]and more fun,[\n]is this going to be the way[\n]I'm becoming the doctor's assistant?
(That's right. <Hatch> was like that[\n]because of 「Rubian」.)
Huh? What the heck?[\n]Is this urgent?[\n]Please rest a little longer.
Besides, the goddess's {Clock Tower}?
That's impossible.
Huh?
Since the day you were blown away[\n]by a cyclone,[\n]the portals has been twisted.
......Huh?
Almost all portals have turned into[\n]『Red Portal』.[\n]It is difficult to procure food.
Hey, this can't be!![\n]But, I must go!!
Okay. At that time, apparently,[\n]<Hatch> said that he was going to[\n]the goddess's {Clock Tower}!
You there...
I just finished it lightly.
Oh... You're back already!
Oh, and the bodyguard![\n]
(Wheez...)
What the heck?[\n]What are you two talking about?
Nothing. Go ahead and good luck.
Oh, and the bodyguard![\n]
(Wheez...)
What the heck?[\n]What are you two talking about?
Nothing. Go ahead and good luck.
To go to {Ludibrium} where the goddess's[\n]{Clock Tower} is located, you have to[\n]take an airship from {Ellinia}.
What, me!?
You're just the bodyguard I hired.[\n]Get out of here!
......Okay.
It was said that dangerous magic[\n]is on it,[\n]if mishandled, disaster will happen.
It's amazing that it's still moving.
It's amazing that it's still moving.
\[name:R_PC\] became a companion.
Are you asking again![\n]The place where the wild boar[\n]is on the right side of the tent.[\n]Get rid as soon as possible.
Mr. <Riness>,[\n]I'm back.
I'll pay you in advance.
Okay, let's start[\n]with the down payment first.
Obtained 『300 mesos』.
<Hatch>, that kid said...
Maybe one day he will be useful.
"I was looking for an opportunity[\n]to test my sword skills..."
......a stupid kid.
Ah... We are practicing[\n]swordsmanship in {Perion}......
Then that's great.
Maple Agent, what's your business here?
Want to be hit by a dull fist?
What... What did you say!
Chill out.[\n]Chill out.[\n]Pretty lady.
......
What's your name?
Yup. My name is \[name:S_PC\].
All right.[\n]Looks like it's been sorted out.[\n]Let's get to work right away.
"......High Priest <Ergoth>'s proposal[\n]accepted by <Sharen VIII>......"
I like my new young friend.
So, let me tell you[\n]what you need to do.
It's a lot stronger[\n]and violent than a normal pig,[\n]so it's difficult to handle it.
Besides, there are only scholars[\n]and workers here, and the only people[\n]who can use swords are[\n]two recent bodyguards.
Since you're an Maple Agent,[\n]I think you can do it alone,[\n]but I'll add a bodyguard just in case.
Help the Maple Agent[\n]get rid of the wild boar!
Ah...!
(The pattern of this guy's necklace is...)
......
Bodyguard!
Yes! I am!
......were you dozing off?
Oh... No.[\n]Thought of something else[\n]for a moment...
You were thinking about something else[\n]during this important conversation!!!
Anyway... This is the second mission.
Hello?[\n]
Who are you?
Yes, this is the first time you've[\n]seen me. I'm Maple Agent[\n]of {Kerning City}.
Maple Agent, what's your business here?
I have something I want to ask.
I'm a busy man.[\n]It's hard to come without[\n]an appointment.[\n]Can you come back?
Hey![\n]Let's take guests to the exit.[\n]
Okay, okay!
Oh...!
What?
I got this from {Excavation Site}...[\n]
Hmm?[\n]....Is it a 「Tablet」?[\n]It's like a {Sharenian} artifact.[\n]
......
"......High Priest <Ergoth>'s proposal[\n]accepted by <Sharen VIII>......"
You...what?
Do you know how to read it!?
Wow. That's great! \[name:R_PC\]!![\n]
For some reason, but...[\n]I have little knowledge, you know?
Are you pretending![\n]It's an ancient {Sharenian} text![\n]Where did you learn that!![\n]
Don't you think he is guessing[\n]around in moderation?
No, some of the texts are decrypted.[\n]It's clearly engraved[\n]with "<Sharen VIII>".
(Well......)
(The pattern of this guy's necklace is...)
It's true.[\n]I don't know why I can read this.[\n]
In fact, he is an orphan and doesn't[\n]remember much from his childhood.[\n]Maybe it's something he learned[\n]when he was a kid.[\n]
Well...
Now, could you read it more closely?
All right, but do us a favor, too.[\n]Please.
Ah, ah, okay...[\n]What do you want?
I'm looking for a gem called 「Rubian」.
「Rubian」......?
「Rubian」... Why are you looking[\n]something like that?
Oh... That's...
We owe it to this guy,[\n]who is a {Sharenian} lover.[\n]He told me to bring[\n]some money or 「Rubian」.
Debt.....?
It's debt.[\n]Woo-hoo, hoo-ha-ha!
Haha haha. Ha ha ha.[\n]Okay, I'll let you know.
Really? Glad to hear that!
But there's one thing I want to ask.
Why don't you listen[\n]to the information after you're done[\n]with it?
Two jobs...[\n]You're trying to sell it at a pretty[\n]high price, aren't you?
I'm sure it's worth it.
I'd rather have faith than[\n]a kind person.[\n]It's okay. Let's do it!
I like my new young friend.
So, let me tell you[\n]what you need to do.
Not long ago, a wild boar have entered[\n]into the {Excavation Site}...[\n]It is interfering the excavation work.
It's a lot stronger[\n]and violent than a normal pig,[\n]so it's difficult to handle it.
I've thought about going out[\n]and catching it myself,[\n]but I don't know where the den is...
Besides, there are only scholars[\n]and workers here, and the only people[\n]who can use swords are[\n]two recent bodyguards.
Since you're an Maple Agent,[\n]I think you can do it alone,[\n]but I'll add a bodyguard just in case.
Hey! Bodyguard!
......
Bodyguard!
Yes! I am!
......were you dozing off?
Oh... No.[\n]Thought of something else[\n]for a moment...
You were thinking about something else[\n]during this important conversation!!!
Anyway... This is the second mission.
Help the Maple Agent[\n]get rid of the wild boar!
Huh? Me too? Sounds like fun![\n]We'll be back!
So, me too!
You stay. Two is enough.[\n]These days, you're probably a little[\n]dull because you're only in the office.
What... What did you say!
Want to be hit by a dull fist?
Chill out.[\n]Chill out.[\n]Pretty lady.
He is thinking of the lady.[\n]The terrain on {Perion} is quite rough.
<Rina>, please stay.[\n]It's dangerous and...[\n]If you stay, I feel at ease.
......
You there...
What's your name?
Huh?
Yup. My name is \[name:S_PC\].
I'm \[name:R_PC\]. Good luck.
All right.[\n]Looks like it's been sorted out.[\n]Let's get to work right away.
The {Excavation Site} is on the right[\n]side of the tent. So, let's get off[\n]to the right end!
\[name:S_PC\] became a companion.
It's over if he can't decipher[\n]the 「Tablet」.
My name is \[name:R_PC\].
The {Sharenian} is a kingdom[\n]that existed about 3,000 years ago.
<Rina> became a companion.
Did you come to your senses?
Most people left after <Riness>[\n]abandoned the excavation team, but...
Me and Dr. <Nuris> are continuously[\n]excavating {Sharenian} ruins here.
But why am I here?
(It seems <Hatch>'s original heart[\n]still remains...)
<Hatch> must be saved!
To go to the goddess's {Clock Tower},[\n]you'd have to take an airship[\n]from {Ellinia}.[\n]Now, 『the portals is twisted』.
I don't know if you can get there,[\n]but are you still willing to go?
Is your body okay?[\n]『The portals is also twisted』...[\n]If you dare to go, I can't stop you...
Huh? Me?
Grandpa!!
Are you better already?
Yes, <Nuris> treated me[\n]in no time. See? It's okay, right?
Who is he?
Ah, hello.[\n]I'm grandfather of these children.
When I entered the tent, I heard[\n]that you offer these children job, so I[\n]unintentionally intervened[\n]in the conversation.
Originally, children were forbidden[\n]to go out when they were young, but...
Today I see that they've grown enough[\n]to achieve things out there[\n]on their own.
Please take care of the children.
Grandpa~ Really?
I appreciate it. I'll take good care[\n]of the children.
I won't need it here anymore,[\n]so I'm going back to {Perion}.
Then, Grandpa goes first.[\n]Since it's your first job,[\n]you have to do it diligently.
Besides, since Mr. <Riness> is willing[\n]to give a job, I am really happy[\n]as old man.
<Hatch>! Did you decide that easily?
I'm going to get permission from[\n]Grandpa later.
I was looking for an opportunity[\n]to test my sword skills[\n]for a long time.[\n]
<Hatch>, but... First of all...
Yes!
Yes!
Handed over the 「Tablet」 to <Riness>.
Yes, this is the first time you've[\n]seen me. I'm Maple Agent[\n]of {Kerning City}.
My name is \[name:R_PC\].
I don't think it's possible[\n]for the bodyguard to do it alone,[\n]but if I send both, security would be[\n]disrupted.
I hope you can do it.
I don't think it's possible[\n]for the bodyguard to do it alone,[\n]but if I send both, security would be[\n]disrupted.
I hope you can do it.
"......High Priest <Ergoth>'s proposal[\n]accepted by <Sharen VIII>......"
"...Protective measures[\n]have been taken.[\n]......afterwards,[\n]......a cyclone blew[\n]in front of the {Sharenian Palace}."
"......High Priest <Ergoth>'s proposal[\n]accepted by <Sharen VIII>......"
"...Protective measures[\n]have been taken.[\n]......afterwards,[\n]......a cyclone blew[\n]in front of the {Sharenian Palace}."
