Look, I found it![\n]I dug up the 「Eye Fossil」[\n]and it was perfect for the statue!
Yes, I found something similar!
Let's put this on the statue!
(......I'm not complaining, but why[\n]are we inserting it like this?)
Now, if you enter this place,[\n]is it {Magatia}?
Two pupils are inserted.
"I am the one who watches[\n]the eternal time."
There's a hole in the stone[\n]that looks like something to fit in.
Two pupils are inserted.
\[name:M_PC\]!
Now, put it in quickly!
It's inscribed with that.
"Those who wish to face me[\n]offer the 『Present Eye』[\n]and 『Past Eye』 to me."
"I am the one who watches[\n]the eternal time."
"Those who wish to face me[\n]offer the 『Present Eye』[\n]and 『Past Eye』 to me."
It's inscribed with that.
There's a hole in the stone[\n]that looks like something to fit in.
It says to insert the 『Present Eye』[\n]and 『Past Eye』 into the stone.
Hmm... It's kind of difficult.[\n]What does it mean?
Come to think of it, I saw[\n]a big-eyed monster flying around.[\n]Does it mean its eye?
Ah, is that the 『Present Eye』?
Yes.[\n]But I...[\n]I'm afraid of that big-eyed monster...
Okay!
Oh, by the way!
Oh, okay. Thanks!
You won't need the 「Stone Spray」[\n]anymore, right?
All I don't need is a burden,[\n]so I have to throw it away.
Ah~ That's a good guess.[\n]Then we can use this 「Stone Spray」[\n]to make it into stone and bring it in.[\n]
Oh...? I saw a sparkling ground[\n]near the seesaw...
Hmm... So what is the 『Past Eye』?
This 「Pickaxe」[\n]and the sparkling ground...![\n] [\n]If you dig with 「Pickaxe」,[\n]wouldn't there be the 『Past Eye』?[\n]
Okay.[\n]Then shall we get one for each other[\n]one by one?
Okay.[\n]Then I'll take the big-eyed monster.[\n]
All right, then take this 「Stone Spray」.
\[name:M_PC\] became a companion.
The .Present pupil. Was to be saved by Mr. [name’\[name:S_PC\]]...
The glowing ground was said to have been seen near where the seesaw was.
I am... You decided to use this 「Pickaxe」 To dig into the glowing ground, right?
It's a guess, but it must have something to do with the 『Past Eye』.
Look at that!!
Now all you have to do is find the 『Past Eye』.
I found it too! 「Eye Fossil」.
Oh, that's great~!
\[name:S_PC\] became a companion.
You don't need a 「Pickaxe」 Anymore, do you?
It's heavy, so I have to throw it away.
I put in the 「Flyeye's Eye」. Sounds right? .The pupil of the present eye. Is correct.
So go ahead and put it on the statue!
Really, what will happen?
Wow, you've already brought it! It's really fast, too.
Wow~~!![\n]Opened.
Wow~~!![\n]Opened.
「Stone Spray」 has been discarded.
「Pickaxe」 has been discarded.
This statue. Isn't it somehow suspicious?
Also...
Right! This was a statue.
It says to insert the 『Present Eye』[\n]and 『Past Eye』 into the stone.
Hmm... It's kind of difficult.[\n]What does it mean?
Come to think of it, I saw[\n]a big-eyed monster flying around.[\n]Does it mean its eye?
Ah, is that the 『Present Eye』?
Ah~ That's a good guess.[\n]Then we can use this 「Stone Spray」[\n]to make it into stone and bring it in.[\n]
Hmm... So what is the 『Past Eye』?
Oh...? I saw a sparkling ground[\n]near the seesaw...
This 「Pickaxe」[\n]and the sparkling ground...![\n] [\n]If you dig with 「Pickaxe」,[\n]wouldn't there be the 『Past Eye』?[\n]
Okay.[\n]Then shall we get one for each other[\n]one by one?
Yes.[\n]But I...[\n]I'm afraid of that big-eyed monster...
Okay.[\n]Then I'll take the big-eyed monster.[\n]
All right, then take this 「Stone Spray」.
I gave the 「Stone Spray」 To \[name:S_PC\].
Yes... Suspicious enough? There seems to be something secret...
I saw this on my way here. If you go[\n]straight to the right and exit,[\n]there's a place where you can 『Save』.
Alright, let's go~
Now, if you enter this place,[\n]is it {Magatia}?
Alright, let's go~
「Eye Fossil」 has been inserted[\n]into the stone statue.
I put the 「Eye Fossil」 On the statue.
It's talking about offering two...[\n]The 『Two Treasure Chests』 I saw earlier[\n]I'm quite concerned...
Shall we go again?
What was written on the statue? I think it has something to do with what I got earlier.
......
I also think that statue has won...
You were also thinking you were suspicious, right?
Yes... Suspicious enough? There seems to be something secret...
Obtained the 「Stone Spray」.
So, shall we get our own eye[\n]and gather here again?
......
I'm a suspicious stone merchant...
What does it look like to say..?
It's talking about offering two things[\n]to the stone...[\n]The 『Two Treasure Chests』 I saw earlier[\n]I'm quite concerned...
Shall we go again?
Oh~ And,[\n]You'll see big-eyed monsters[\n]if you go to the right.
I see.[\n]To the right?
I saw the sparkling ground on the left.
Oh~ And,[\n]You'll see big-eyed monsters[\n]if you go to the right.
I see.[\n]To the right?
I saw the sparkling ground on the left.
So, shall we get our own eye[\n]and gather here again?
Okay!
