Oh! It leads here![\n]It's fun!
......Blemish...
By the way... Where is this?
......Huh?
!!!
\[name:S_PC\]!
Come on, come on, come on, wait!![\n]What do you mean?
Shut up![\n]Do you think I can be fooled!?
I really don't know.[\n]I have nothing to do with it now!
......
I came here to defeat <Riness>[\n]and get my friend back!!
You mean the blue-haired guy, right?[[\n]Where's he?
If it's <Hatch>, he's over the portal[\n]on the right, but...
To the right?
Don't move!!!!!
A girl whom has been seen somewhere[\n]is chasing a monster.
Do you know the monster who mutters[\n]while running away?
To the right?
I'd better take it quickly.[\n]Because, it's dangerous.
Being dangerous means that...[\n]Are you talking about that big octopus[\n]earlier?
You... Do you know <Papulatus>?
The octopuses crossed into {Ellinia}[\n]on an airship...[\n] [\n]These guys ate the airship parts[\n]and ran away...
Hmm? I think we're at {Excavation Site}[\n]of the {Sharenian} ruins.
Eh? {Sharenian} ruins? Here?
......Oh, I remembered!
Eh?
...Hmm.[\n]I think it has...
Uh......
!!!
Glad I meet you here.
Come on, come on, come on, wait!![\n]What do you mean?
......
That's because <Riness> has something[\n]to do with...
As expected!!![\n]So, you were an enemy!!
I really don't know! I don't know!
You mean the blue-haired guy, right?[[\n]Where's he?
That guy is not normal right now.
Hey, you <Rina>don't really know where you're going, right?
Insistence really! I don't know!
Found!! This guy!
Oh...
Did you run over there?
Do you know the monster who mutters[\n]while running away?
My, that's right.
I'd better take it quickly.[\n]Because, it's dangerous.
Being dangerous means that...[\n]Are you talking about that big octopus[\n]earlier?
(<Papulatus>Ramen... <Roberto> I've heard from the captain as well.)
I was chasing the octopus[\n]that ate the parts.
By the way... Where is this?
......Oh, I remembered!
Eh?
Uh......
Hey...
Ah, that's not the case, I just heard it from the researchers in {Magatia}.
So what <Papulatus>do you know about well?
In addition... The story was so difficult that I almost forgot about it...
Oh... That, yes.
Ok thanks!!
Yes. I heard the {laboratory}[\n]created <Papulatus>...
Sound... Is it the {Sharenian} ruins {Excavation Site}?
Eh? {Sharenian} ruins? Here?
You, obviously,[\n]did you meet <Manji> in the tower?
I am the one who sings the Ruins......
Oh! What did you do!?
I, I'm sorry!![\n]Don't tell me, really...[\n]With my 『song』...
Well... it just feels brighter,[\n]it looks better, but...
I'm so sorry!
The octopuses crossed into {Ellinia}[\n]on an airship...[\n] [\n]These guys ate the airship parts[\n]and ran away...
I actually have one.[\n]Look, here.
Have you ever done this with my 『Song』......
(<Papulatus>Why is the legion of {Sharenian} headed?)
<Riness>It's probably there.
\[name:S_PC\]!
So, why are you here?
I came here to defeat <Riness>[\n]and get my friend back!!
\[name:R_PC\]!
Where is <Rina>?
But... my friend's shock was great,[\n]I don't know what to do...
{Magatia}?
By the way, where is this?
You, obviously,[\n]did you meet <Manji> in the tower?
I actually have one.[\n]Look, here.
Do you know the 『Song』 Of {Sharenian}?
{Sharenian}......[\n]It's a civilization that brought[\n]a manastone with tremendous power,[\n]「Rubian」, into this world.
By the way,[\n]did you talk about <Manji> earlier?
Oh! What did you do!?
I, I'm sorry!![\n]Don't tell me, really...[\n]With my 『song』...
I'm so sorry!
Oh, I shouldn't be doing this![\n]I have an urgent business, bye!
Oh? Well, okay.
She's a very busy girl.
Oh!
So the 『Trash Can』 with the letter[\n]thrown away is beyond that portal?
Hmm??? What is it this time?
Are those toy monsters from this side?
Nope. Now is more important than that<Hatch>, not the time!
Looks like we've passed through the {excavation site camp}?
I really don't know.[\n]I have nothing to do with it now!
I see. Those toys came from here.
Anyway, it doesn't matter about this. <Rina>You have to find it!
...Hmm...
Anyway, I can't afford to think about something like this right now.
What, octopus......... Is it a toy? I haven't been there before...
But... I didn't have those guys before...
<Rina>You have to find it!
Sound? Are you back again?
Your friend. It looked bad... For once, I felt like I was looking for you.
...... <Hatch>.
Anyway, I'm not going to get involved because complicated things are enough for now.
Oh yes, but where did you say this is?
Here? This is the {Excavation Site} near {Perion}.
So to get to {Ellinia}, would it be faster to take a taxi from {Perion}?
Yes... What's the matter? Because {Perion} is not far from here...
From here, go all the way to the left, and you'll see {Perion}.
(If it were {Perion}, <Manji>I don't know if I would be able to meet Mr. Lee as well.)
......Is this the part box the captain was talking about?
I have obtained the .Born Parts Box..
It's a part of the same color as the appearance. That said, it's a monster that was originally modified by eating this part, so of course it is.
You like. I found one! Now there are 4 left.
It's a bit strong, but it's also a good level to perform...
But where the heck is these guys moving towards?
Stand there!!
Is that octopus sent by <Papulatus>?
I heard it when I went to {Magatia}.
{Magatia}?
However, the Toy Corps[\n]also invaded this place.
Hmm...
But you keep bothering me. I feel bad about it.[\n]
Hmm...
Is that octopus sent by <Papulatus>?
I heard it when I went to {Magatia}.
Yes. I heard the {laboratory}[\n]created <Papulatus>...
However, the Toy Corps[\n]also invaded this place.
I was chasing the octopus[\n]that ate the parts.
...
If you take a taxi from {Perion}, you'll be able to get to {Ellinia} in no time.
......
Ah... no...[\n]I just... didn't get an answer...
Hey...!!!
Uh... Yes...
But you,[\n]why are you screaming and fussing!!!
But...[\n]What were you thinking?
......
Hey...
......
Hey...!!!
Uh... Yes...
But you,[\n]why are you screaming and fussing!!!
Ah... no...[\n]I just... didn't get an answer...
But...[\n]What were you thinking?
......
Do you <Papulatus>know about it?
......
(If it were {Perion}, <Manji>I don't know if I would be able to meet Mr. Lee as well.)
Why do you know me?
Ah, no.[\n]It's not that I know,[\n]it's just that I've seen it.
Oh... My name is \[name:S_PC\].[\n]I'm from {Perion}.
I...
If so, are you also related[\n]to 「Rubian」?
\[name:A_PC\]. {Henesys}.
Why do you know me?
Ah, no.[\n]It's not that I know,[\n]it's just that I've seen it.
Oh... My name is \[name:S_PC\].[\n]I'm from {Perion}.
I...
\[name:A_PC\]. {Henesys}.
By the way,[\n]did you talk about <Manji> earlier?
If so, are you also related[\n]to 「Rubian」?
...Hmm.[\n]I think it has...
「Rubian」became strange[\n]because you sang!
Well... it just feels brighter,[\n]it looks better, but...
Good bye!
As expected!!![\n]So, you were an enemy!!
Glad I meet you here.
Where are the flippers![\n]I know your friend kidnapped <Lina>.
I really don't know! I don't know!
「Rubian」became strange[\n]because you sang!
Oh, I shouldn't be doing this![\n]I have an urgent business, bye!
Oh? Well, okay.
Good bye!
\[name:R_PC\]!
Where is <Rina>?
Where are the flippers![\n]I know your friend kidnapped <Lina>.
Shut up![\n]Do you think I can be fooled!?
Because it really is![\n]It's been a while since I was fired![\n]It's because I lost to you last time!
Are you serious?
But... my friend's shock was great,[\n]I don't know what to do...
Huh. <Hatch>, you must have come to your[\n]senses after bragging about learned[\n]a few tricks from that old man?[\n]
The old man has nothing special except[\n]that loud shout after all.
After all, there are only \[name:R_PC\][\n]who can fight on an equally with me.
In fact, can he even beat me[\n]if I fight seriously?
Huh?
What just happened?
I think I just said something strange...
Also... <Hatch>![\n]No matter how much I think about it,[\n]it's too much![\n]
You pushed me off that cliff,[\n]didn't you?
Argh! If you move on to this point,[\n]you are a loser, right?
Next time I see you,[\n]I'll pay you back!
Hmm...
There seemed to be something...
I feel like someone is chasing me.
Hmm... It's weird.
Hmm...
Eh?
Could it be that monster?
So shall we go?
\[name:S_PC\].
Hmm...
Ugh... You... What are you doing...
The heirloom you had is really 「Rubian」.[\n]
Ugh... How do you know...
I heard you all talking[\n]to the girl earlier.
I'm sorry, but I'll take this.[\n]I'm sure 『Riness』 will be pleased[\n]if he sees this.[\n]
<Hatch>!
<Hatch>!
Ugh...
<Hatch> took away the 「Rubian Piece」.
That's because <Riness> has something[\n]to do with...
The mood has changed.
Yep, I came when I caught a wild boar! Above this is the .Blast zone., and that is the entrance to the {Sharenian} ruins.
Are you serious?
Huh?
Have <Hatch> kidnapped your friend?
If it's <Hatch>, he's over the portal[\n]on the right, but...
To the right?
That alone is complicated enough[\n]for me.
If it's a lie, I won't let it go!
Have <Hatch> kidnapped your friend?
Because it really is![\n]It's been a while since I was fired![\n]It's because I lost to you last time!
Are you serious?
So, why are you here?
That alone is complicated enough[\n]for me.
That guy is not normal right now.
If it's a lie, I won't let it go!
What's going on?[\n]That guy is really excited, isn't he?
Huh? You what?
If you understand it roughly, go ahead.
Why do you suddenly do that?
Huh? What did I just say?
You just looked like a different person for a moment...
Who?
......It's weird.
Hurry up and chase <Hatch>.[\n]He'll give 「Rubian」to <Riness>.
I must stop him.
I have obtained the .Born Parts Box..
At last... That is the last part! You like! Now that we've got it all together, will we go back to {Ellinia}?
(First, let's go back to {Perion} and <Manji>meet .)
(I think it's better to leave <Hatch>[\n]alone for a while.)
When there,[\n]the Toy Corps raided.
When there,[\n]the Toy Corps raided.
