......!
<Rina>!!
\[name:R_PC\]!!
It's alright!?
Stay away from this guy!!
\\\[name:R_PC\\\], not that!
What!!???
......
I just did...... It was a dream that seemed to be happy.
After all, <Ergoth>this was the only thing he wanted.
Yep, happy and...... It easily turned into a nightmare because of it.
After that, it took me 3,000 years to finish the back.
<Manji>Seed...... Already?
More than that, you. What the heck is identity?
I'm <Manute>like, the specter of a {Sharenian} who couldn't die.
3,000 years ago, in an attempt to seal the 「Rubian」That had flooded into my own 『Song』, half of me was taken away by the 「Rubian」.
He tried to flood 「Rubian」With 『Song』 And seal 「Rubian」... So, if you......
Right. <Ergoth>Neither am I.
On that day 3,000 years ago, the runaway 「Rubian」Was split into four pieces and scattered all over the place.
<Ergoth>His weak and young mind became a monster by integrating with a piece of 「Rubian」.
Horsepower is in the 「Rubian Piece」, and reason is on me.
<Ergoth>Seed...... There was one thing I wanted to ask.
\\\[name:R_PC\\\], ...... I'm so sorry. I've dropped your family in Hell.
Even now, 3,000 years later, I used you to take care of the situation. ...... You can't be forgiven.
......
I'm sorry, <Sharen>son of .
<Siria>Get along well with a lady who resembles you.
......Where are you going?
One more person, someone to apologize for...
......Can't you meet them now?
I'm originally a dead body. 3,000 years ago. Now all you have to do is get it done.
It's a farewell.
Hi... <Manji>.
......\\\[name:R_PC\\\], <Manji>after all, what was Mr. Lee's identity?
He was an old friend of my father. So......
Anyway... It's a long way to talk about.
...... <Manji>Mr. Lee said he saw a sign of something...
Light?
Maybe that's it!
And, I have leftover debris.
And, I have to send you guys back here to the original world.
You'll see a sign. Walk towards it.
I lost my strength, and for the next 3,000 years, I was watching four pieces of 「Rubian」.
Let's go back! \\\[name:R_PC\\\]!!
......The king of {Sharenian}, that is, <Sharen>the king ......
River...... Father...... Is that correct?
......
Also...... He was the father.
You buy...
I said I had something to say before, remember?
Huh???
When this is over, I have something to say... You said that in The Blast Zone.
I?
What... What the heck... You! How curious were you while you got here?
Huh? Did you expect something?
Yes! Do you remember? Speak fast! What was the point of talking?
Neither will it be today. That's the next time I'm talking about it~
Let's get out of here first.
Hi... <Ergoth>.
This......
......Perhaps, this is what the kid really wanted.
Only this...... All I wanted, alright, something like this......
Obtained the 「Rubian Piece」.
......
Did you say that?
