Whoa... Whoa![\n]The vibration doesn't subside!
Why... What's wrong? What's going on?
My friend told me[\n]never to break the altar.
Still, the vibration doesn't subside.[\n]I don't think the altar is broken...
Whoa![\n]The vibration is subsiding.
The vibration has completely stopped!
Ah... It looks strong, right?
You won't know without fighting.[\n]If we work together, we can win!
Ye...Yeah!
I don't know about that, but I don't[\n]think it can be avoided for sure...
Was that what was inscribed[\n]on the stone statue earlier,[\n]『who watches the eternal time』?
Incredibly big!
......
Good![\n]Here we go!!!!!
Huh!
Now... Hold on!! Let's go together!!
Oh... What is that?
The altar?[\n]What happens if you break it?
He said a big deal was going to happen.[\n]Maybe I'll never him again.
Oh my god~!!!
Whew~ That's a relief.[\n]I was really surprised earlier.
Maybe... Was this what <Manji> said?
Is it really calmed down?
I don't think the altar is broken.
Huh!
Oh... What is that?
Incredibly big!
Was that what was inscribed[\n]on the stone statue earlier,[\n]『who watches the eternal time』?
I don't know about that, but I don't[\n]think it can be avoided for sure...
Ah... It looks strong, right?
You won't know without fighting.[\n]If we work together, we can win!
Ye...Yeah!
Good![\n]Here we go!!!!!
Now... Hold on!! Let's go together!!
(But...[\n]And... Can we win by joining forces???)
Whoa... Whoa![\n]The vibration doesn't subside!
Maybe... Was this what <Manji> said?
Why... What's wrong? What's going on?
My friend told me[\n]never to break the altar.
The altar?[\n]What happens if you break it?
He said a big deal was going to happen.[\n]Maybe I'll never him again.
Oh my god~!!!
Still, the vibration doesn't subside.[\n]I don't think the altar is broken...
......
Whoa![\n]The vibration is subsiding.
Is it really calmed down?
The vibration has completely stopped!
I don't think the altar is broken.
Whew~ That's a relief.[\n]I was really surprised earlier.
