Whoops... The crane seems to be broken.
Is this the .Pupil of the present eye.? But how do I take it...
You like. You like. It's hardened. So now I have to go back to the front of the statue. But is that guy doing well?
Ok! You can use 「Stone Spray」 To make it into stone!
!!!
That's what the big-eyed monster[\n]was talking about.[\n]Anyone can recognize it at a glance!
So let's see if there's a time. If I find the .Current pupil., I will go to the front of the stone statue.
Hey! I finally found a place where the big snow monsters were gathered!
Wow, congratulations.
You haven't found it yet?
Yes... I'm still there.
Ok? Maybe you'll find it soon.
I got the 「Salt Shoes」.
Huh, because I'm not the right size...
Pooh! Sounds like it's precious to pretend to be, right? Are you really giving it to me?
Oh... I hear the sound of wings.
Yes... I think it's a little deeper.
I think I saw it from the inside out too.[\n]
......Where is the big eyed monster?
Ah, yet.
I see. I'm still there. I need to go a little deeper.
Cheer up!
Sound!?
Oh! It was you. Did you find the 『Past Eye』?
Shhh
You've been here. Has there been some progress?
It's only a matter of time!
Oh yes, and take this. I grabbed the monster and picked it up.
