Press 『\[A\]』 to attack[\n]the enemy in front of you.
Right now, I'm testing my Charged Attack ability. You are not allowed to go outside during the test.
Right now, I'm testing my Charged Attack ability. You are not allowed to go outside during the test.
Oh, you're a new testinee.
A Charged Attack is simple .if you press and release the \[A\] button for a long time..
At this time, the longer you press, the more the .Attack Force. will be counted, and the wider the .Strike Range..
However, if you press for too long, you will become tired and unable to move for a while.
So, use a Charged Attack to take down the monster across the street.
So, use a Charged Attack to take down the monster across the street.
Very nice. This course is a pass.
However, there is still a test left, so you can continue to the left.
Please use Charged Attacks. .If you press and release the \[A\] button for a long time, it will be.. Isn't it just that the button was pressed a little shorter?
You have to use a Charged Attack to take down the monster across the street. .If you press and release the \[A\] button for a long time, it will be..
So, please try again.
At? You have already passed this course, but... Do you want to practice holding attacks more?
Are you confident in the degree of Charged Attack too?
Can I reiterate the explanation?
Yes, please explain it one more time.
No, that's fine now.
Hold attack is a success. This course is good enough, so you can continue to the left.
Yes, I'd love to do a little more.
No. Now there's plenty of practice.
Please come to my door.
Hiik~
This is the place to test your 『Charged Attack』 skill.
Oh boy... Ahead......... Yes... Four.
(Qa... It's a surprise!)
