Oh, you're a new test taker.[\n]Do you know how to 『Dash』?
Wow~ It's amazing that you're doing[\n]『Dash Jump』. There's usually good stuff[\n]hidden in difficult place.
Press 『\[<\] or \[>\] twice[\n]quickly and holding it』.
There are no monsters or obstacles[\n]in this area, so it's a good idea[\n]to practice 『Dash』 as much as you want.
Oh, the portal is gone again.[\n]I don't think this is a coincidence.
Oh~ There are new portals this time![\n]They're red! It might be[\n]connected to something great!
But...[\n]I need to hurry up[\n]to get to the village.
Oh!
The portal...!
I need to hurry up.
