!!!
What amazes you so much?
Anyone who shows up anywhere like that is bound to be surprised. But somehow until here...
Come to think of it, there was one thing I didn't teach you...
A special skill of the Magician, called .teleport..
Do you mean the art of pressing the \[R\] to move instantaneously?
!!! Did you know?
I'm not familiar with it yet, but one day I saw what my grandfather was doing and tried to imitate it.
Huh... Huh... I can't believe it. I learned it just by watching the teleport.
So I said I didn't learn it, but I did it.
......Ok, so it is practiced until you use it familiarly!
At!!! Even if you suddenly say that, I'm still ready...
So you're going to create an obstacle in front of this, so follow me through it.
So, like me, come here without ever being harmed by teleporting.
Ok. Well said! I'm a little relieved now.
!!!!!!!
What's wrong?
I just had a strange aura that was obvious...
Go ahead. I have to finish the test.
Hmm. Was it my mistake? Anyway, when the test is over, hurry up and come back.
...!!! What was it just about? Somehow a strange feeling.
Where to run! Perfect your teleportation and pass by!
Yes! Oh, okay.
So, as soon as the test is over, go to town...
With teleporting, you can avoid the attacks of monsters as well as dangerous objects as you do now,
You can also go back to the monster's back and fight from an advantageous position.
Hiik~~!! The portal is gone!
I also didn't like these tests from the beginning. I need to get back to town quickly.
You can teleport with the .\[R\].. During the teleport, there is no damage.
All three obstacles must be passed without being hit. Calmly look at the streets and use them.
How do you use teleports? Just press the \[R\]. Now, try to stay calm once again.
Are you trying to teleport unduly while walking or dashing?
Teleports can be used by standing still and pressing the .\[R\].. Now, try to slow it down once again.
You don't have to say more about using teleports as .\[R\]s., right?
You can get close enough to avoid reaching obstacles and then teleport. One by one, one by one.
