You see, three of those monsters somehow! Can I do it?
Acquired the 「Energy Bolt I」 skill.
You've mastered the skills. To date, it is an excellent grade.
At? I? Are the grades really excellent?
Yes, it is an excellent grade. However, the test is not over yet. From now on, the training to use the skills will begin.
Again... Training? Just give up at this point...
This is the last step,[\n]so keep up your spirit.[\n]The rule is simple:
When the test begins, monsters will appear. Then you can do it with the skills you've just mastered.
Press the \[L\] to use the energy bolt..
You are not allowed to go outside during the test.
.Press the \[L\] to destroy all the monsters with energy bolts..
The tests are all over. You can also return to town.
.Press the \[L\] to destroy all the monsters with energy bolts.. So, let's start over.
It was a nice energy bolt. This technique is the art of creating an energy sphere and throwing it head-on.
Now, you can go back to town.
Hiik~ comes this way!
Even~
????
The tests are all over and you are allowed eligible to use your skills.
The energy sphere has the .property of penetrating enemies. and is therefore .more useful when dealing with multiple enemies..
All skills 『Consume MP』 and[\n]MP displayed as 『Blue Bar』[\n]in the upper left corner on top screen.
All skills 『Consume MP』 and[\n]MP displayed as 『Blue Bar』[\n]in the upper left corner on top screen.
E~ By the way... Are you just going?
Yes, you can go.
Maybe it's public transport or school buses... Is there anything like that?
At??? Yes, such a thing is not ready. You can walk comfortably.
......Yes.
Hiik~~!
So, let's get started.
Ah, I forgot to say,[\n]but all skills 『Consume MP』.
MP is displayed as 『Blue Bar』[\n]in the upper left corner on top screen[\n]and will recover if you stand still.
Ah, thank you. In this case, you just say, .If you stand still, the MP will automatically recover.?
You need to assign the skill[\n]by pressing 『(START)』,[\n]but this is your first time,[\n]so I will assign it in particular.
