It's saved well.[\n]See you later~
Hi. I'm here to help adventurers.[\n]
Please save your adventure,[\n]so you can continue from there later.[\n]
So every time you see me,[\n]you'd better save it.[\n]
And don't be surprised if you see me[\n]outside in a different way. Because[\n]that's what it looks like.
I'm planning to sell things to help[\n]travelers. It's still being prepared.[\n]Please come back later~
Hi. I'm here to help adventurers.[\n]Are you going to save your adventure?
Yes, I'll save it.
No, I'm just going.
Okay, then...[\n]Please be careful!
Now then,[\n]are you going to save your adventure?
Yes, I'll save it.
No, I'm just going.
Okay, then...[\n]Please be careful!
