............
(Where are you <Panda>going to go?)
&^&_)(*~!
What, what?
......Are you telling me to come up?
Now, it's up. How are you going to do it?
............ ...... Up there?
$%^+@#
......Climb? Up there?
(What the heck...?)
(nod)
(KU Took)
Oh, <Panda>hey! I'm experimenting with someone I don't know! No! That's a crime!
*&$$#$!!!!
Huh? Create a man-made human being who can defeat aliens? If you give it an electric shock, it turns into a man-made human? Did you see it on TV?
No, if you believe the TV of the Earth so naively~. Lying?
(Black...)
.#$+9_)(
Huh? Don't you want to be conquered by other aliens before you conquer it? Need a load?
Still, <Panda>hey, you need money to hire people. Look, this guy is going to eat a lot of food, right?
<Panda> Do !!! Want to die this guy!!!
Ego~, sorry~. We <Panda>had a lung injury~.
......Aw,~ Looks like a temper!!
This kid is a panda-type alien who is working hard to conquer Earth.
This is the {Omega Sector} fighting aliens that have invaded Earth, right?
That's right~. A bad alien has invaded~.
This child, far from conquering the Earth, aliens have invaded and are in a state of distress.
Poor thing? Now, <Panda>hey, you can conquer the Earth by all means!  Git up! Let's go!!
............!
......Ah, yes...... Cheer up......
Anyway, I want to go to {Ludibrium}, but don't you know the way?
No. <Panda>I'm just a traveler.
For more information, please ask the doctor above here~. You can take the .Elevator on the left..
(Well, what.... This event... It didn't mean anything!?)
It's about conquering the planet with strength. It's about guiding foolish people.
Defeat the bad aliens. Without losing your smile, you will go to Go-Go-Think!
......What is it? What happened to me now?
Operating table? Experimental device? Why are you on this list?
Huh? What is it? Why does it seem so enjoyable? What, what, is that switch?
......
Not good, right? This is a bad situation to look at, isn't it?  Now, wait......
Oh, <Panda>hey I'm experimenting again! No! It's a crime!
%$+_./??!!
At? Are you using someone you picked up from the road to keep your lungs from hurting?
Ah,
Hermitage, Human, lived...!
Mountain... Is that a thing? This thing.....
But <Panda>hey, is he a weak person?
*&#$;/*
Even if I renovate it, would it only be about the average person? If you just hit your toes, you'd fall, right?
Black and black... For the first time I see a kid...... I'm not .Looking weak., I'm being told that I'm .weak.....
&*9+_#$5
Huh, to no avail, so let's send it back?
@#&*
I'm back alive, but I don't have a chance at all...
..........
Over there! Did you help......
......Once you know, once aside, thank you anyway.
Ah aha~ It is also the duty of a talent like us to take care of foolish citizens.
Yes~? ...... Oh, so be it... But where is this?
This is {Omega Sector}, fighting bad aliens who are trying to conquer Earth. Isn't it, <Panda>dude?
*&6@#/*!!!
That, black and white... Who is he?
<Panda>We're really stalwart pandas aliens trying to conquer Earth alone.
I would say that the flow of the story right now is quite strange, but it seems contradictory.....
How so?
No, it was anyway. Do you know of a portal to {Ludibrium} rather than that?
Well, I don't know what's difficult! There's a doctor upstairs, so ask.
_)*(&6@#4!~~
Huh? Would that person be good to renovate too? The person who came from somewhere else and dropped the UFO?
Huh? Is there anyone from another place? Where now?
But, haven't you seen that guy lately?
Wooing, I don't know! I don't have enough time to figure out the trends of every single stupid citizen.....
Oh, you see...
Who was the artificial candidate who dropped the UFO? I'm not back here~
Whoaaaaaa!!!AAA
......Huh,~billion, huh,~billion, huh,~billion...
Ugh... Ugh......
Wait, that guy...?
Her huh!!
%$+_./??!!
(...... Sounds good, but...)
(These people, I was even subjected to electrical torture next to me... The report doesn't have any response at all, right?)
(Are these people insensitive? Are you used to this kind of sight?)
......By the way, what the heck is this guy?
Huh? The way to {Ludibrium}?
I don't know it's that difficult. Ask the doctor upstairs for a difficult problem.
You can take the elevator on the left.
This guy... Are you laughing at me this time? Benefit... Let's leave it at that.
(<Panda>Seeing that reminds me of that pain earlier.)
(You didn't even bother to let me be electrically tortured next to me, did you?)
(Is it a frequent sight here...?)
(He, by the way, these people...)
.........Here?
$%^+@#
Here? Stay here?
(nod)
(What the heck...?)
(KU Took)
Whoaaaaaa!!!AAA
Oh, <Panda>hey! I'm experimenting with someone I don't know! No! That's a crime!
*&$$#$!!!!
Huh? Create a man-made human being who can defeat aliens? If you give it an electric shock, it turns into a man-made human? Did you see it on TV?
No, if you believe the TV of the Earth so naively~. Lying?
(Black...)
......Huh,~billion, huh,~billion, huh,~billion...
.#$+9_)(
Huh? Don't you want to be conquered by other aliens before you conquer it? Need a load?
Still, <Panda>hey, you need money to hire people. Look, this guy is going to eat a lot of food, right?
<Panda> Do !!! Want to die this guy!!!
Ego~, sorry~. We <Panda>had a lung injury~.
......Aw,~ Looks like a temper!!
......By the way, what the heck is this guy?
This kid is a panda-type alien who is working hard to conquer Earth.
This is the {Omega Sector} fighting aliens that have invaded Earth, right?
That's right~. A bad alien has invaded~.
This child, far from conquering the Earth, aliens have invaded and are in a state of distress.
Poor thing? Now, <Panda>hey, you can conquer the Earth by all means!  Git up! Let's go!!
............!
......Ah, yes...... Cheer up......
Anyway, I want to go to {Ludibrium}, but don't you know the way?
No. <Panda>I'm just a traveler.
For more information, please ask the doctor above here~. You can take the .Elevator on the left..
(Well, what.... This event... It didn't mean anything!?)
