From here on, it's a battlefield. It is very dangerous.
Huh? UFO? ...... No, good luck.
The operation of the light declaration is simple. Press .\[^\]. On the cross button close together to take aim.
Did you shoot down a UFO? He is amazing. It's unbelievable.
When the enemy comes into range, it fires with the 『\[A\]』. The angle is fixed, so you need to aim well.
The operation of the light declaration is simple. Press .\[^\]. On the cross button close together to take aim.
When the enemy comes into range, it fires with the 『\[A\]』. The angle is fixed, so you need to aim well.
From here it is the battlefield. It is very dangerous.
The operation of the light declaration is simple. Press .\[^\]. On the cross button close together to take aim.
When the enemy comes into range, it fires with the 『\[A\]』. The angle is fixed, so you need to aim well.
Elegant~ What's this!
That's great~ If this is the case, you can kill the aliens in a blow!
