Oh, you're a new test taker.[\n]Do you know how to 『Dash』?
Wow~ It's amazing that you're doing[\n]『Dash Jump』. There's usually good stuff[\n]hidden in difficult place.
Press 『\[<\] or \[>\] twice[\n]quickly and holding it』.
There are no monsters or obstacles[\n]in this area, so it's a good idea[\n]to practice 『Dash』 as much as you want.
Oh... The portal is...
『Red Portal』...?[\n]I'm sure there's[\n]a new red portal just now.
The portal to the town looks dangerous.
Whoa...
The portal...!
If we don't hurry up,[\n]we won't be able to go back to town!
