Oh, you're pretty good. But from here,[\n]『ranged attack monsters』 appear.
The door is locked.[\n]It can only be opened with a 「Key」.
Huh?...You need a 「Key」, right?[\n]Maybe the 『monster』 has it.
Nothing happens.
This door is locked.[\n]But if you have a 「Key」, you can[\n]open it. Here's how to use it.
1. Press 『(START)』[\n]  to open main menu.[\n]2. Select 『ITEM』.
You're a warrior, so 『Guard』 will[\n]blocks ranged attacks.[\n]Press 『\[R\] to Guard』.
Okay! It's open~
Oh!
Lots of monsters.[\n]This is a great chance[\n]to use 『Power Strike』!
Hi, I'm a fairy who helps you[\n]under the orders of the goddess.
Please save your adventure,[\n]so you can continue from there later.
I'll be there before dangerous area,[\n]so every time you see me,[\n]you'd better save it.
Oh, I'm sure you have seen me[\n]in the village as a fairy.
I'm hiding it, so keep it a secret.
Now then,[\n]are you going to save your adventure?
Yes, I'll save it.
No, I'm just going.
Okay, then...[\n]Please be careful!
It's saved well.[\n]See you later~
Hi, I'm a fairy who helps you[\n]under the orders of the goddess.[\n]Are you going to save your adventure?
Yes, I'll save it.
No, I'm just going.
Okay, then...[\n]Please be careful!
What...?[\n]What was that?
(Hmm... I can't use my skills because[\n]I don't have enough MP.[\n]If I do nothing and stand still,[\n]MP will recover, right?)
Is this the 「Key」?[\n]What is this for?
This is a... 「Key」.[\n]Is it the 「Key」 to open the door?
3. Select (「Key」) item to use it.
Saving also restore both HP and MP,[\n]which will help you on adventure.
