It's a red portal!!
HU HU HU, you are indeed my eternal rival, King.
It's easy to come back, and you're going to knock me down again!! This is fate, King.
Okay, okay, that's it...
King!!
King?
The owner of a sharp, thin sword and a slender body?
......You know... At...
Hu, you are indeed my eternal rival. King.
You! Then that's <Fugitive>!
Come here with ease, drive me back to the corner!! This is fate, King.
What are you talking about!!
But!!!! But, but!! I, too, have passed through the 2nd round to a new realm!!
......???
Gather your burning passion in a hat, red shadow 3 times faster!!
Gamma, which means the third! Victory initials!!
.Fledgling Mid-Range Fighting Gamma.!! This horror, you will taste, King!!
If you keep doing that, are you going to hit it again?
Anyway, I'm not here to catch you.
You, have you ever seen a pale blue-haired man here?
Saw it!
I took the red portal over there.
Are you serious!? If you lie, you won't forgive me!
When I'm serious, my tone is also serious.
King!
(Somehow, it's suspicious... I don't know, you <Rina>know......?)
Where's it now?
......Ugh. I'm going to say it now.
Huh? Is this connected by the {Subway}?
You can't climb up there with a flash jump?
......Well, it doesn't matter because there's another road to {Kerning City}.
Huh? Here, something like {Subway}?
Yes, that's right! I came here through there.
So, would you like to be able to get to {Kerning City} through here?
......You can't climb up there with a flash jump.
......Well, it doesn't matter because there's another road to {Kerning City}.
I see. It's definitely like a {Subway}.
\[name:R_PC\]. This place sounds like the {Subway} of {Kerning City}?
So if you go up there, you can go to {Kerning City}, right?
......Well, it doesn't matter because there's another road to {Kerning City}.
But, that height would be unreasonable even with flash jumps?
Huh?
No doubt!!! I've found an exit![\n]
<Hatch>~
<Hatch>~!
What's going on~?
I found a red portal on this side!
Oh! Good!
I'll go with Grandpa~!
!!!!
Grandpa!!!
Grandpa!!!
Why did you get here...
Grandpa didn't come back,[\n]so I came looking for you.
Grandpa, are you okay? [\n]I think you've hurt a lot...
It's okay. I just got hurt a little[\n]while jumping from a high place.
There's a lot of monsters here,[\n]so we'll have to get out[\n]to a safe place first...
I'm going to find a way, so[\n]<Hatch> please take care of Grandpa.
Are you sure you're all right alone?
Of course. Don't worry.
Sorry, I'm becoming a burden to you.
I will take care Grandpa.[\n]Don't worry, just look for an exit.
Hmm...
Ah, now that I think about it, I think I've somehow seen it.
(The guy who used to go with the red-haired warrior?)
What the heck?  Is there anyone who picks up?
Well, there's a guy who comes to mind.
The direction that disappeared is also on the {Excavation Site} side <Riness> .
You said you went out to the red portal at the far left.
You don't want to change your mind and catch me again, right? King.
Thanks anyway. Well done a good job.
Do you think it's your victory? King!
Don't hit me, don't hit me! Rowdy guy! King!
Huh?  Oh... Blue-haired guy?
Don't freak out, tell me quickly!
Carrying something heavy...
That sack of bags, a little wriggling...
He's always been with the red-haired warrior guy...
You're one of those guys I hired the other day as a part-time job when I was being chased by you and a sleazy Magician.
(Really, that guy!)
