Oh! I think it's kind of right?![\n]It also makes sense...
Great! I'll have to bring it[\n]to \[name:M_PC\]!
I already have 「Goblin’s Song」,[\n]but...[\n]Should I do it a little differently?
......
Huh? Nothing happens?
.....
Come to think of it... All I've gathered is a 「Song Piece」.
Like my grandmother said, if you put the song in that tree, you'll know the right order.
Huh? I kept not knowing... What's that?
!!!
Should I write the songs here in order?
Maybe only 3 of 5 songs hidden[\n]by the goblin were real?[\n]
What is it?[\n]I'm sure there was something...
!!![\n]It's somewhat...
Go away~[\n]Leave the song... Go away~
You want me to go away?[\n]...It's kind of creepy.
!!!
Nothing happens anymore...
Trip~ Thunderbolt~ Sang~
Nothing happens.
Is the order wrong?
As such, I'm not sure because the order is messed up.
Is this the Song Tree?
Anyway, first of all,[\n]I have to collect the songs.
Suspicious nostalgia?
Go away... Leave the song~
Wow, here is the whole 「Goblin’s Song」 Brought by Mr. \[name:S_PC\].
I think I've written it down here.
.The red light is orderly, the red light is the time. Time is the scale, the world is the scale. It is the wand of the goddess that calms the world..
It says:
The tree has
Obtained the 「Goblin’s Song」.
Hmm, isn't there much else to do?
I don't need to see it anymore.
!!!
Is this the Song Tree that Grandma spoke of?
Should I arrange the songs here in order?
Maybe only 3 of the 5 songs that the imp hid were real, right?[\n]
What is it?[\n]I'm sure there was something...
!!![\n]It's somewhat...
Go away~[\n]Leave the song... Go away~
Go away... Leave the song~
You want me to go away?[n]...It's kind of creepy.
So you collected all 5, right?
You like. Write down the songs in the 「Song Piece」 Collected here in order.
Is there a lack of 「Song Piece」?
