Maybe...[\n]Is this old man the captain?
Who do you see as old man?[\n]This body is Captain <Roberto>.
(Huh, after all, he's the captain...)
Ho~ Oh~[\n]As expected~[\n]The king is very thoughtful.[\n]
I was having a hard time getting[\n]outside because of the monsters...
Yes...
Anyway... I came to find you[\n]at the request of the king.
I've never heard of a monster[\n]leaving a portal when it dies.
There's a monster on the top too. It's hard to go back to this...
Is Monster Handling Yet?
So, go ahead and let the surrounding monsters kill and open the way.
I'm going to take a break. Let me know when the surroundings are cleaned up.
Go in first.[\n]I'll go in after you.
If so,[\n]is it a monster creates portal?[\n]Was it a monster that ate portal?
......Or has the portal turned into[\n]a monster...
(You're so embarrassed by the person who came to your rescue.)
The monster is fought above seems to be[\n]a variant monster that was born when[\n]the second portal anomaly occurred.
Just thinking about it doesn't give[\n]an answer.
I have no choice but to go through[\n]the portal.
I'll take care of it.
The speed was a little better on the Archer side earlier...
Hmm...
It's to yourself, so don't bother. I've had something similar before, so I've only thought about it for a while.
The monster left a red portal.
Go in first.[\n]I'll go in after you.
Maybe...[\n]Is this old man the captain?
Who do you see as old man?[\n]This body is Captain <Roberto>.
(Huh, after all, he's the captain...)
Anyway... I came to find you[\n]at the request of the king.
Ho~ Oh~[\n]As expected~[\n]The king is very thoughtful.[\n]
I was having a hard time getting[\n]outside because of the monsters...
But...[\n]It looks like you've already cleaned up[\n]your surroundings.
Oh, are you a little faster[\n]than that archer?
(......Archer?)
Anyway...
......
