Tomb of <Sharen II>... It is...
Now, there seems to be nothing.
Tomb of the third king...[\n]Maybe there's something[\n]on that tombstone?
[\t]I've been told that drinking drinks stored in storage warehouses is safe from ghost attacks.
!!!
This monster.[\n]My attack doesn't work at all![\n]What happened!
Also...[\n]My attacks aren't working at all.
$%% @\[- @#!*^ a*crib# ±^#!#$+=|@ *&!) ± &^$@#*
[\t]Huh? What is it? Who is this person? Could it be a ghost???
[\t]At... But it doesn't seem to be a dangerous ghost.
☆$%% @\[- #$+=|@ # a*crib# ±^#! *&!) ± &^$@#* !*^
Hmm... I still don't understand.
But where is <Hatch>?
Obtained the 「Valve Handle」.
[\t]Mankind... Your strength... Definitely looked.
[\t]You can move on.
[\t]Sound? There's something else between the tombstones...
!!!
This monster.[\n]My attack doesn't work at all![\n]What happened!
Also...[\n]My attacks aren't working at all.
Is there any other way to defeat it?
[\t]Lots of rag ghosts to show.
[\t]It's quite spacious. It's like a huge warehouse.
It's kind of creepy here.
[\t]What... What the heck! Those black rag guys... You look eerie.
It's kind of creepy here.
What the heck...[\n]These are the guys whose attacks[\n]didn't work.
It won't be easy here.[\n]What should I do?
[\t]AAT!
[\t]These guys, the attacks don't work!
[\t]Are you angry because you hit it?  The atmosphere got rough.
[\t]Pooh! What a surprise!
[\t]It's not that easy here. Let's take a sigh and think about it.
[\t]Laughs ha~
[\t]What the heck is underneath?
[\t]Those guys, the attack didn't work... This is dangerous.
[\t]Laughs ha~
[\t]It's quite spacious. It's like a huge warehouse.
[\t]Lots of rag ghosts to show.
[\t]What the heck is underneath...
[\t]\[name:R_PC\]! Look there!
[\t]What... What the heck.
[\t]Ball... The attack doesn't work, does it?
[\t]Here... Vaguely... Looks like a dangerous place.
[\t]Ok. Let's go up and think again.
[\t]This guy! Cowardly ambushing!
[\t]You have a taste too!
