Hey~
...? What are you talking about?
Oh!
AAAAA
......
When I hike, I usually go to areas where there are no icicles... Work. Work. Work.
What... It just means smashing it if you have time and going.
Yep, it's a body that has been tempered by mountaineering ever since. You can go back on your own.
Thank you, thank you. I could barely go back.
At...
Oh... Ah, I'm fine. Thank you so much for saving me from the ice.
But you're the first face you see... What brought you here?
Yes... I have something to investigate.
But is that really okay?
By the way...
I think it's okay to break this icicle.
I want to do something in return... I don't have anything now.
The next time you stop by the village, come to visit me. I'll definitely reciprocate...
So, I'm going to be twenty-one. See you.
I want to do something in return... I don't have anything now.
The next time you stop by the village, come to visit me. I'll definitely reciprocate...
Where's the place to get hurt?
