Oh! \[name:R_PC\].[\n]I heard you're taking the test again.[\n]Good luck...
Wow~ It's amazing that you're doing[\n]『Dash Jump』. There's usually good stuff[\n]hidden in difficult place.
Haha! Not this time.
Of course you know, but rule is rule.[\n]Then I hope you pass.
If you forget,[\n]you can 『Dash』 by pressing[\n]『\[<\] or \[>\] twice quickly and holding it』.
There are no monsters or obstacles[\n]in this area, so it's a good idea[\n]to practice 『Dash』 as much as you want.
Ah... The portal is gone again.
Huh? What's that?[\n]It is portal... Isn't it?[\n]But... That portal is strange.
The portal to the city seems[\n]a bit odd. I need to hurry.
Oh!
The portal...!
I have to go quickly before it's gone.
