<Helena>, the union leader, is not here.[\n]Can you please wait a little?[\n]I will come to you soon.
Oh, that's fine. You don't[\n]have to look for it on purpose....[\n]Instead, pass this item to <Helena>.
Oh? Oh~! Oh~!
What's wrong?
Could it be that \[name:A_PC\][\n]your job this time to find a 「Jade Ring」?
Yes..
So, you came here after killing <Lupin>,[\n]who lives in the depths[\n]of {Sleepy Dungeon}?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, what a ~~~ \[name:A_PC\].
Don't be so surprised.[\n]It was a little difficult for me too.
Then I'll just go.
Ah~ \[name:A_PC\]. You're back.
Yes, hello. <Helena>.
What a relief. Just come back...
The 「Jade Ring」 was delivered to <Maple Agent>.
Ah, thank you.[\n]I'm sorry for asking \[name:A_PC\],[\n]who is not even a Maple Agent,[\n]to do something cumbersome.
That's ok, <Helena>.[\n]It is my pleasure to help others.
Thank you. \[name:A_PC\].[\n]I'm so sorry, but I have one more favor.[\n]
Huh?
In fact, the situation is a bit urgent.
If it's just a monster, shouldn't[\n]Maple Agents handle it themselves?
Of course... I was going to, but...
The union leader!
No! What about the wound?
It's okay. More than that, right now...
<Helena>, you're in terrible injury.[\n]Okay. Where is the test site?
It is 『the left end of town portal』.[\n]
Yes, then I'll go.
This is a portal.[\n]You can go to another area by[\n]pressing 『\[^\]』 on the portal.
Somehow, a strong monster[\n]invaded the test site.
Let me get to the point.[\n]The 『Skill Licensing Test』 is currently[\n]underway in the suburbs of {Henesys}.
Ugh...
Leave the union leader to me[\n]and hurry to the test site.
Don't worry about me,[\n]please go to the test site.
Simply follow the 『Red circle』[\n]shown on the screen below.
Huh? Direction? Head to the portal[\n]on the right, then head to the far[\n]left of the town.
I gave the 「Jade Ring」 to <Maple Agent>.
