Oh! You've been waiting there![\n]Have you finally resigned yourself!!
I mean,[\n]the word 『resignation』 itself is weird...
Now brake slowly...
Hi, I'm a member of the Carriage Club.
While driving, you can jump[\n]by pressing 『\[B\]』.
What should I do?[\n]I don't think there's any other choice[\n]but to go down this hole, right?
It looks deep...[\n]Would that be okay?
This job has a good payoff.[\n]Yeah, let's go!
If there are obstacles while runnning,[\n]you can avoid them by jumping,[\n]so keep that in mind.
Oh! You've been waiting there![\n]Have you finally resigned yourself!!
I mean,[\n]the word 『resignation』 itself is weird...
Do you know how to jump on a cart?
What did I say earlier?[\n]You...you didn't listen to me.
If there are obstacles while runnning,[\n]you can avoid them[\n]by pressing 『\[B\]』.
What should I do?[\n]I don't think there's any other choice[\n]but to go down this hole, right?
It looks deep...[\n]Would that be okay?
This job has a good payoff.[\n]Yeah, let's go!
Whoops.[\n]If you underestimate me,[\n]you'll get hurt, kwang.[\n]Please give up at this point.
Ugh......
What are you doing! This guy!!
Right! What are you doing!!
Huh? Still alive, kwang![\n]What a tenacious vitality.
But, now you know that it's dangerous[\n]to chase me, kwang.[\n]Go back quickly, kwang!
Hey... You seem to be[\n]misunderstanding something...
We just wanted to ask[\n]if you saw my Grandpa around here.
?[\n]???
You guys,[\n]aren't you Maple Agents, kwang?[\n]You're just looking for Grandpa, kwang?
Maple Agent?
Ah, no, no, no,[\n]nothing, kwang.
I'm actually being chased by the bad[\n]guys right now, kwang. I mistook you[\n]for them, kwang.
Hehe~
Are you going to let it go[\n]with 『hehe~』?
Ah, no, no, no...
Are you looking for your grandfather who is tall-headed, kwang?
Oh, that's right.[\n]Where did you see him?
Not too long ago[\n]when entered {Subway}, kwang.[\n]Now, I don't know where he is. It must[\n]be somewhere in the {Subway}, kwang.
Did you come here to work?
That's right, kwang![\n]You guys, won't you do a part-time[\n]job, kwang?
Part-time job?
Something's fishy....
No, no, no,[\n]it's not suspicious at all, kwang.[\n]It's fair and square, kwang.
If you help me, I'll help you[\n]find your grandfather, kwang.
You're going to find him!?[\n]Shall we! Shall we![\n]I want to work part-time!!
Hey, look...[\n]We need to hear what kind[\n]of part-time job it is.
It's easy, so don't worry it, kwang.
So follow me, kwang.
