Thief!!! Surrender now![\n]There is no place to escape.
Hahaha~ Is that so?
You're still bluffing, Thief!!![\n]But today you'll surrender.
Haha~ Don't push your luck.
Hey, hey~[\n]How long are you going to do that?
If I don't do this,[\n]I'll probably go crazy.
So why are you making such a mistake?
People sometimes make mistake.
How can you catch a petty thief[\n]but mess up the {Construction Site}?
You know......[\n]That's called a mistake.
Eh~~ I don't do it intentionally,[\n]stop talking about it now!
Thanks to your mistake,[\n]the construction around {Kerning City}[\n]has been extended indefinitely.
Well~ We've got a lot of work to do[\n]since you're off work anyway.
\[name:R_PC\]![\n]\[name:R_PC\]!
Ah... What is it this time?
\[name:R_PC\]! Where are you!
It's downstairs. <Rina>.
Oh no~[\n]I knew you'd be like this.
What is it this time?
Do you know what day it is?
Today??? Um... It is <Rina>'s birthday, isn't?
You! When was the last time[\n]you went outside?
So eh...[\n]3 weeks ago or 4 weeks ago...[\n]maybe 5 weeks ago or 6 weeks ago...
It's the day of the 『Skill Licensing[\n]Test』!!! If you pass,[\n]you can work as Maple Agent again!
Huh? 『Skill Licensing Test』?
Okay! You didn't even register, did you?
Yeah, I didn't...
I'm going to go ahead and pick it up,[\n]so hurry up and come towards[\n]『the left exit of the village』.
Thank you.[\n]I'll be right there.
Yeah~ Today is the last day[\n]of my jobless life.[\n]So, excuse me~
Ah, I forgot about it,[\n]but it is today. Go ahead.
You can go up and down by pressing[\n]『\[^\] or \[v\]』 on ropes or ladders.
What are you doing,[\n]you're going to be late.
This is a portal.[\n]You can go to another area by[\n]pressing 『\[^\]』 on the portal.
However, it's too much[\n]to 『ban for using skills』[\n]on incumbent Maple Agent.
