Oh? Where is this?
!!!
Found! That's it! Wait!
......Is this the part box the captain was talking about?
It's a part of the same color as the appearance. That said, it's a monster that was originally modified by eating this part, so of course it is.
Obtained the .Green Parts Box..
You like. I found one! Now there are 4 left.
But where the heck is these guys moving towards?
Where the heck did the big octopuses go?
It's a bit strong, but it's also a good level to perform...
Obtained the .Green Parts Box..
At last... That is the last part! You like! Now that we've got it all together, will we go back to {Ellinia}?
