By the way... Kinda weird?
!!!
<Papulatus>Isn't this the {Magatia Laboratory} in the memory of .
Try. Doc. The infinite power latent in that red gem...
But, that's it. It's so powerful. If you touch it incorrectly, it's dangerous.
It's an accidental discovery, and you don't have to give it back, so let's study it carefully.
Doc. If we find a way to control that gem...
Ok... If only I could control it.
Here...... {Magatia Laboratory}!
{Magatia Laboratory} was clearly in ruins...
......
{Magatia} could rule the world.
No magic or science can create this level of power.[\n]
The {Magatia Laboratory} in his memory...
I see!!
If this is <Papulatus>the past, there will certainly be times when he's still weak.
If I hurt it then, I think things will be easily solved.
......
So <Papulatus>let's go find the past?
What's wrong?
Oh... You are welcome.
!!!
Here...... {Magatia Laboratory}!
......
By the way... Kinda weird?
{Magatia Laboratory} was clearly in ruins...
<Papulatus>Isn't this the {Magatia Laboratory} in the memory of .
The {Magatia Laboratory} in his memory...
I see!!
If this is <Papulatus>the past, there will certainly be times when he's still weak.
If I hurt it then, I think things will be easily solved.
......
What's wrong?
Oh... You are welcome.
So <Papulatus>let's go find the past?
