\[name:R_PC\], is something written?
Where, where?  This, this......
.One day, suddenly, the portal becomes strange and splits up to the sky....
.From there a multitude of demons poured out, and in an instant the whole world was covered with demons. I don't know how long I'll be safe..
Roughly that... It's written......
Not really... {Sharenian} Doomsday?
......
\[name:R_PC\], why? It's alright?[\n]
It's so eerie. The heavens are divided, and the devil's hordes ... Too bad and afraid.[\n]
Something I didn't remember, I think I would remember...
It's so eerie. The heavens are divided, and the devil's hordes ... Too bad and afraid.[\n]
Now that I've figured out where 「Rubian」Is. ... But....
It's the driving force behind the portal. If you touch it, it could be a big deal...
We can't do that.
......How's that?
Uh, isn't that guy that monk a little while ago?
This, hey, monk, what's going on? It's hurtful, isn't it?
Sounds like you need to heal sooner than that?
Leave here quickly. We'll guide you to the exit.
The temple was raided by the villains. You are outsiders, so avoid them before you are upset.
But you can't run away, can you?
I'm worried about other people...
.One day, suddenly, the portal becomes strange and splits up to the sky....
.From there a multitude of demons poured out, and in an instant the whole world was covered with demons. I don't know how long I'll be safe..
It's unpleasant to read it a few times. I'm afraid I keep coming...
It's been 3,000 years, and I feel a sense of terror as if I had seen it myself. What's wrong?
Something I didn't remember, I think I would remember...
......It's like a testament.
<Mr. Wang>I'm going to have to take you to the ruins of the {Sharenian} and ask them to be satisfied enough to see the .Ruins..
First, let's go up and look at the situation!
