!!!
Ua~~!!! It's a monster!
Get out of the way!! Get out of the way!!
(Maple Agent is not decent......)
Is that guy?  <Blue Dragon Turtle >, which is definitely a bit of a bummer, but...
Was this guy who was the one who was in question at the test site?
The problem seems to have been solved, but... Now that you're here, let's go to the end.
Using the .Backstep. that allows you to look ahead and step back will make it easier to win.
If you run away now, it's just a laughing stock.
If you run away now, it's just a laughing stock.
So, can you take a look at your hands?
By pressing the \[R\], you can use the Archer's special technique, the .Backstep..
!!! Portal!!!
Is it gone?
What's going on? Would be nice to go back to town now.
Correct! Because .Backstep. Feels like this! It's much more comfortable to use during aiming.
