The door is locked.[\n]It can only be opened with a 「Key」.
Hmm... Where do I get the 「Key」...[\n]Does the 『monster』 have any?
This door is locked.[\n]But if you have a 「Key」, you can[\n]open it. Here's how to use it.
Nothing happens.
1. Press 『(START)』[\n]  to open main menu.[\n]2. Select 『ITEM』.
Yeah! Opened.
!!!
Yeah! If there's a monster[\n]in such a difficult jump position,[\n]chance to use 「Lucky Seven」!
Hi, I'm a fairy who helps you[\n]under the orders of the goddess.
Please save your adventure,[\n]so you can continue from there later.
I'll be there before dangerous area,[\n]so every time you see me,[\n]you'd better save it.
Oh, I'm sure you have seen me[\n]in the village as a fairy.
I'm hiding it, so keep it a secret.
Now then,[\n]are you going to save your adventure?
Yes, I'll save it.
No, I'm just going.
Okay, then...[\n]Please be careful!
Hi, I'm a fairy who helps you[\n]under the orders of the goddess.[\n]Are you going to save your adventure?
Yes, I'll save it.
No, I'm just going.
Okay, then...[\n]Please be careful!
It's saved well.[\n]See you later~
...!?[\n]What is it......
(Hmm... I can't use my skills because[\n]I don't have enough MP.[\n]If I do nothing and stand still,[\n]MP will recover, right?)
Is this the? 「Key」? Where do I use it?
This is a... 「Key」.[\n]Is it the 「Key」 to open the door?
3. Select (「Key」) item to use it.
Saving also restore both HP and MP,[\n]which will help you on adventure.
