Oh, you're a new test taker.[\n]Do you know how to 『Dash』?
Wow~ It's amazing that you're doing[\n]『Dash Jump』. There's usually good stuff[\n]hidden in difficult place.
Press 『\[<\] or \[>\] twice[\n]quickly and holding it』.
There are no monsters or obstacles[\n]in this area, so it's a good idea[\n]to practice 『Dash』 as much as you want.
Ah... I have to hurry.

??? Ahh This time we have a new portal! But this portal is something strange... I don't want to go into that portal anyway.
Ugh, the portal to the village would be dangerous!
Ah
The portal...!!
