Doctor, wait...
Oh, it was you. Ok. What is going on?
As you may have felt, I think it is almost impossible to crack the code of the red gem with our own strength.
Sound... Interesting.
Thread... I've already created a few kinds of pseudo-creatures.
Oh! Interesting. You, when did you do that research? Come on, let me show you!
If you could .Synthesize similar creatures. Of a docile nature on a red jewel...
This is the idea that came to mind, but...
Hmm...
Wouldn't we be able to control the power of that gem by domesticating similar creatures?
Interesting, but...... It's uncertainty.
