Oh...... Ugh...... Here...... Where ?...... My head is dumbfounded......
Research...... Room? How to!? Suddenly I got out of the {Clock Tower}!
......Here, above...... From earlier... Hammer... Keep twirling around the same place..
The innermost part of the goddess' {Clock Tower} is the end of this world,
No, my head is so dizzy.
<Papulatus>I'm here to take it down.
By the way, here, strangely because the space is a mess......
The 「Rubian」Of this wand is planted with a code to control the 「Rubian」.
......I don't have an answer.
Shall I try that? The last thing I did on {Maple Island}.
As it turned out, Mr. [name:A_PC\] was .The one who sings 「Rubian」., right?
The situation of finding a portal somewhere is the same as it was then... Let's do it.
The 「Rubian」Of the cane...
It was great! If you go to the side where this sound rings strongly, maybe...
Ok~
Thank you!
If it weren't for you, I might have been stuck here all my life.
Let's go ahead!
Is it a sham?
So who do I look like?
By the way, how come you are in a place like this?
<Papulatus>I'm here to take it down.
He told me <Papulatus>to knock him down and come to 「Rubian」.
Ok...
......That's right.
By the way, here, strangely because the space is a mess......
This place is...
The 「Rubian」Of this wand is planted with a code to control the 「Rubian」.
Nevertheless, the gem of that wand was 「Rubian」!
As a matter of fact...... I went <Papulatus>to the runaway because of my inadvertent actions.
I took responsibility for that...
I don't know what you're talking about. You were runaway because of your inadvertent actions...
Anyway, for now, the two of you have to work together to get out of here.
Yes.
......I don't have an answer.
Shall I try that? The last thing I did on {Maple Island}.
As it turned out, Mr. [name:A_PC\] was .The one who sings 「Rubian」., right?
The situation of finding a portal somewhere is the same as it was then... Let's do it.
The 「Rubian」Of the cane...
It was great! If you go to the side where this sound rings strongly, maybe...
Do you think you can get here?
That's right. Thanks to Mr. \[name:A_PC\].
Words of Stars. The same goes for the one that rolled my feet around.
Let's go ahead!
But here... It's like you've seen it somewhere...
The real world is...... Nope. ...... No, common sense in our world doesn't work...
Now, as far as hearing......
......Wait, really...... A human voice? Does anyone have one!?
Ugh... Ugh......
......Huh?
I couldn't go any further, so I was rolling my feet in circles.
Nevertheless, the jewel of that wand was 「Rubian」!
You, has it changed a lot?
Pooh!! Found!
Ugh... Ugh......
......Huh?
......\[name:A_PC\]Mr.?
Woman... The goddess's command... Consenting?
Unlike in the past, it's good to be motivated, but...
I couldn't go any further, so I was rolling my feet in circles.
If this is the case, you <Papulatus>will be able to weaken the power of .
If this is the case, you <Papulatus>will be able to weaken the power of .
You, has it changed a lot?
It was great!
I was told that the bottom of the {Clock Tower} is the end of the world and mixed with the chaos outside the world.
......\[name:A_PC\]Mr.?
Huh?
I had been wandering around here before I met you, but there was no exit from here.
Wherever I go, I'm still here.
Hmm...
Ok! Right!
It's me who is grateful. I was able to find it thanks to the 「Rubian」You have.
Where's this...
The head is dizzy.
<Papulatus>The feelings I felt outside were conveyed more clearly.
What, what! What are you going to do if you suddenly want to give it a try?
It's dangerous to swing like that all of a sudden.
MER... My head hurts a little... I didn't think I saw anything in vain.
I'm going to catch someone who has only seen the twice.
Hick~ that... Not like that... Four... Please spare me.
<Papulatus>I'll take it down. There's a good way for me.
(Oh... No. \[name:A_PC\] <Papulatus>is trying to kill you!)
(Never! Never!)
What are you mumbling to yourself?
You two can fight together. Rather than just worrying about it uselessly, it's now a global crisis.
Oh... So... Approval.
<Papulatus>It's like the spirit of the world. <Papulatus>I feel a lot of different emotions.
When I walked in here, I felt a tremendous rush of emotion.
So Git.
(You can't let Mr. \[name:A_PC\] <Papulatus>fight with me.)[\n]
......
Huh? You, really\[name:M_PC\] are you right? Could it be a sham?
Is it a sham?
What, what! What are you going to do if you suddenly want to give it a try?
Hick~ that... Not like that... Four... Please spare me.
It's dangerous to swing like that all of a sudden.
He~ By the way... You're really right \[name:A_PC\]! Nice to meet you!
He~ By the way... You're really right \[name:A_PC\]! Nice to meet you!
So who do I look like?
MER... My head hurts a little... I didn't think I saw anything in vain.
I'm going to catch someone who has only seen the twice.
By the way, how come you are in a place like this?
Woman... The goddess's command... Consenting?
He told me <Papulatus>to knock him down and come to 「Rubian」.
......
What are you mumbling to yourself?
<Papulatus>I'll take it down. There's a good way for me.
Unlike in the past, it's good to be motivated, but...
Ok...
You two can fight together. Rather than just worrying about it uselessly, it's now a global crisis.
......That's right.
This place is...
<Papulatus>It's like the spirit of the world. <Papulatus>I feel a lot of different emotions.
Oh... So... Approval.
When I walked in here, I felt a tremendous rush of emotion.
As a matter of fact...... I went <Papulatus>to the runaway because of my inadvertent actions.
I took responsibility for that...
I don't know what you're talking about. You were runaway because of your inadvertent actions...
Anyway, for now, the two of you have to work together to get out of here.
So Git.
Yes.
\[name:M_PC\] became a companion.
\[name:A_PC\] became a companion.
Beauty... I am sorry. I just casually ...
