[\t]\[name:A_PC\]~ Hello~
[\t]<Helena>Wouldn't it be a good idea to tell you the facts about the song even now?
[\t]Oh boy... Hi. The first face you see? I'm sorry, but there was a rush...
...What are you talking about?
[\t]Why did you lie?
[\t]...... What are you talking about? Don't know a single one?
[\t]If you go to {Ludibrium}, you might not be able to do anything~.
[\t]Looks like you just made a mistake? Again, what's going on in {Ludibrium}?
[\t]Oh my gosh~ I made a mistake~
Kyaaa!
Help me!!
......[\n]Hmm...
Huh, what? ...scream?
Are you alright!?
Huh? ....yes.
Strange, isn't it?[\n]Monsters like this appear[\n]around the village...
Yes, I saw such a big monster[\n]near {Henesys} for the first time.
({Henesys}......)
Yes. Thank you very much.
[\t]It's gone...
[\t]Four, save me!! Kamak!!
({Henesys}...... Looks like there was[\n]something to be done in {Henesys}...?)
(That's right,[\n]after falling off the cliff,[\n]I slipped into the river below...[\n]and it came to this point...)
[\t]Kamak~
[\t]Can anyone please help me~?
[\t]That girl. It's definitely a crisis! You like! I'll save you.
[\t](People have appeared!)
[\t]......
[\t]...... What was it?
[\t]Huh???
[\t]E~ By the way... To get from here to the {Excavation Site}... How do I get there?
[\t]Would it be better to take a? .taxi. In the village rather than walk?
Thank you.
Anyway, I'm glad you are safe.[\n]It's dangerous here, please go home.
Ugh... Where am I?
As expected...[\n]I don't know even if I look at it.
<Hatch>, you punk![\n]I stopped you because I was worried.[\n] [\n]But, you pushed your friend off[\n]the cliff?
Ok. Do whatever you want.[\n]Now I don't care what happens to you.
[\t]Ugh... What do you think happened to {Henesys}?
