Why? You're somehow weird, too?
......That kid. He's not talking.
<Hatch>???
!!
......I have to say a word to that woman, I just can't go back.
Now, put your 「Rubian Piece」 in there.
Your brother, no......
......You, were you weaving with your brother from the beginning?
The substitute of {Sharenian} <Ergoth>had been in pain for 3,000 years.
I gave him a 「Rubian」That was too much for a human being to bear, and he was doomed to a great fate.
And because of that... Even to you... I struggled a lot.[\n]
......That's it. It wasn't something I did for you anyway...
Was it for yourself?
It was for everyone, including me.
Yeah~!
......That way too<Ergoth>... I think I had a relationship with Mr. Lee.
Hello. I think the \[name:R_PC\] guy has caused a lung without me knowing......
(Huh, I had a girlfriend! Unbelievable!)
Sound...... Who was it?
......At the {Excavation Site}, I was embarrassed.
<Papulatus>It's not dead.
「Rubian」...... <Papulatus>Let's give back the transgressions.
Now, put your 「Rubian Piece」 in there.
Because of this,[\n]he...
That's what humans are.
They make a lot of mistakes[\n]and learn a lot from it too.
<Papulatus> is a living creature,[\n]and they all think of him as a monster.
After all, everyone...
......
Ah?
Yeah, I think you're done safely.
\[name:M_PC\]! I haven't seen you in a while!
Was your research at the {Grand Library}[\n]succeeding? I'm glad!
{Sharenian} You met at the {Excavation Site}.
Did you help \[name:S_PC\]?[\n]Thanks. Because of it, I'm saved.
Don't blame yourself too much.[\n]<Papulatus> won't blame you either.
Now, put your 「Rubian Piece」 in there.
<Ergoth>I need to get your 「Rubian」Back properly.
Father, Mother, <Ergoth>Mr......
Thank you for sending me into this world.
I'm gone, no worries about myself. That would be nice... Joe?
The three of you will be delighted. In the kingdom of 3,000 years ago.
......Ok.
\[name:R_PC\], that's great... Isn't it a little weird to say?
Hey~!
Hey~!
I've caused you a lot of trouble.[\n]I'm sorry.
I think <Fire Phoenix>'s baby was born[\n]safe and sound.
I owe you. I... I'm not confident yet,[\n]but I have something to do...
No, it's changed a lot![\n]You can be confident!
You can't just take 「Rubian」Like this.
Now, put your 「Rubian Piece」 in there.
Then <Hatch>...[\n]Shall we go back to {Perion} now?
......Do you know.
I'm not going back.
Huh? What do you mean?
I... I'm going to go to {Sleepywood}.
Of course, that's not the only reason.[\n]I'm going to train my mind now.
<Hatch>...[\n]You got the answer.
I was grateful about {Grand Library}.[\n]Thanks to \[name:S_PC\],[\n]everything went well.
Hey~[\n]......Well, anyway,[\n]I'm glad you made up with your friend.
I just kept struggling[\n]because of you guys![\n]Haha.
I'm sorry.[\n]I don't know what to apologize...
Now, wait,[\n]Aren't you taking this seriously!?[\n]It's a joke, a joke!!
Is this the deepest part of the goddess' {Clock Tower}?
Clock......
May be... <Papulatus>Isn't it near here?
This is the source of the 「Rubian」, the deepest part of the goddess' {Clock Tower}... Is it the case?
It's a huge clock.
So is this the depths of the goddess' {Clock Tower}...
...There's something incredible[\n]about the clock.
That's right.[\n]Is this the...[\n]center of the goddess's {Clock Tower}?
Ah!!!
Ah!!??
<Riness>. I'll close my eyes for[\n]what happened with that bald head.
Thanks to you guys,[\n]I've only gotten needlessly fatigue!
Oh! Then your guy did something weird on 「Rubian」!!
...Who is it?
......
Oh! May be... Did you meet on the bridge?
We'll see you again one day.
The girl who used to whine that she had[\n]lost her 「Boarding Pass」.
There's a clock that looks like something deep-storyd...
Oh!! Here is the {Deep Clock Tower}!
....We are back.
<Hatch>.
Hey <Hatch>!
!!!
<Hatch>!
!!!
Now portals like this are not the problem. Once <Hatch>you're done!
<Hatch>!![\n]
(Oh... Now is not the time to do this. <Hatch>I'll have to take it with you!)[\n]
<Hatch>?
Why, <Hatch>!
That kid...[\n]He doesn't even move from earlier.
<Hatch>...
Doesn't blink an eye.[\n]He's just breathing.
Who are you talking to?
Hey![\n]What are you looking at?
Uh, uh.. Huh???
What! Don't you see my friend[\n]who just walked over there?
.....
Also, to say...[\n]It was all because of 「Rubian」is,
{Sleepywood}?
I think it's too cowardly of me.
To you who've been with us[\n]all this time,[\n]to Grandpa who raised us...
And...[\n]
I want to live begging for forgiveness[\n]from Mr. <Riness>.
But...[\n]That's all...
I also got my own answer[\n]from this trip.[\n]Please don't stop me.
「Rubian」or <Ergoth>...[\n]I won't lose to anyone anymore.
I think,[\n]I've come up with a cool idea...?
Hmm?[\n]What did I just say?
Oh~! Is that so?[\n]To protect something precious?!
...........
Well,[\n]you'll find out when you live again!
The scattered 「Rubian」must be gathered[\n]together and the balance of this world[\n]must be corrected.
The portals in this world won't be[\n]twisted, in the future.[\n]At least for quite some time...
Thank you.[\n]Thanks to that, we can bring the world[\n]into balance.
<Hatch>!
<Hatch>.
<Hatch>?
Hey <Hatch>!
Why, <Hatch>!
Are you still angry with me?
He was your friend, right? I haven't said anything since earlier.
<Hatch>...
Hey!
......
Hey...?
......
Right! I said I knew this person \[name:S_PC\] and I knew...
Hey?
...
Huh? You what?
...
What really... Are you kidding me?
Don't you hear me?
......At the time, I thought it could be anything...
Are you distracted?
!!!
There's someone over there.
I'm going to ask you for directions...
But what...
Are you ignoring me now?
......
......
Did you go out of your way to be dumbfounded?
Yes, <Papulatus>I'm first finding it now.
......I have no choice but to leave it at that.
<Hatch>, what happened!
What the heck happened? Aren't people going to disappear...
......
Yes, here...?
......
He was just lonely...
He just needed a friend...
He just needed a family...
Didn't you also gain more than you did[\n]on your first trip?
You look so depressed.
I can't tell you, but...[\n]Let's just say it's a reward[\n]for returning 「Rubian」.
<Papulatus> is not dead.
......
Just now...[\n]Goddess, what did you say?
<Papulatus> he's not dead.
He's alive a little far away.
But... Obviously...
What you see isn't always true.
After a little time,[\n]when the world finds its stability,[\n]we will able to meet him again.
Huh...[\n]This is what the goddess is saying...[\n]I should believe it, right?
Yes.
Glad to hear that.
Thank God.
Yay!!!
Yay!!!
<Papulatus>!
Surely...
A friend!
I'll be waiting.
He'll definitely come back!!!
Nothing happens.
Nothing happens.
Nothing happens.
「Rubian Piece」 is inserted.
「Rubian Piece」 is inserted.
「Rubian Piece」 is inserted.
「Rubian Piece」 is inserted.
Nothing happens.
\[name:S_PC\], help me.
<Hatch>......
<Hatch>.
Hey <Hatch>.
Please talk to me!
......That kid. He's not talking.
Doesn't blink an eye.[\n]He's just breathing.
<Hatch> What happened!
!!
<Hatch>???
Who are you talking to?
<Hatch>!
<Hatch>......
Hey![\n]What are you looking at?
What! Don't you see my friend[\n]who just walked over there?
(...... What are you talking about.)
<Hatch>.
Hey <Hatch>.
Please talk to me!
Uh, uh.. Huh???
!!!
What the heck?
What, where did it go?
......It was as if I had been sucked into this man's body...
Right. Obviously... It felt like being sucked in.
Ugh...
Don't worry. <Hatch>, I'll save you.
But how do we get here?
This guy used to be {Excavation Site} on the bridge...
I don't blink an eye.
This guy, not moving at all. What happened?
Hey man!!!
......
Hey, that guy, you know?
He's a bit weird.[\n]He doesn't move at all.
Even his eyes don't blink,[\n]he just seems to be breathing.
Huh?
Thank you.[\n]Something like 「Rubian」is something[\n]we don’t need anymore.
Rather, I almost lost something[\n]precious because of this.
......
You have a pure heart.
I appreciate it.
Glad to see you.[\n]You're back to the real world.
The space you entered earlier[\n]was a distorted space created by[\n]an abnormality in 「Rubian」.
Thanks to you defeating <Ergoth>,[\n]the original {Clock Tower} has returned.
Oh... I see.
......
By the way... Who are you?
Hello. I am <Minerva> who manages[\n]the {Clock Tower}.
<Minerva>...?
Where did I hear it...?
Right![\n]It's the name of the goddess <Minerva>!
Huh?
The goddess?
Is she the goddess?
Yes, I am a goddess <Minerva>.
......
<Hatch>! She said goddess!!!
It's unbelievable.
......
A long time ago...[\n]I gave a manastone to help humans.
But... As a result,[\n]it has caused humans great pain.
There was a lot going on, but...[\n]
I also think that 「Rubian」should not be[\n]in the human world.
Now, please return 「Rubian」here.
Yea...yes.[\n]Su...sure!
Okay...[\n]It's something we don't need.
\[name:A_PC\]?
Hi?
\[name:R_PC\]!
You're a little late.
And over there... \[name:M_PC\]!
Ah, \[name:S_PC\] welcome back.
Why here...
Then I'll go back.
Wait a minute. There's still work left.
Huh? What's left?
Yes, please wait for the other pieces to come together.
Oh... So why don't you just wait?
Yes, great. I'll wait.
Sure thing... Everyone was waiting for the purification of 「Rubian」Like that.
Yes.
Yes, great. I'll wait.
That's why everyone was waiting like[\n]that for the purification of 「Rubian」.
Yes.
Okay!
Yeah, I'm ready.
Yes, I'm ready.
Ok... Okay! I'm in!
<Hatch><Rina>Please step back to the left for a moment.
......
I want to help too!
This ritual should be conducted only[\n]with these four of the purest heart.
I see.
I know you want to help,[\n]but I can't help it.
......
Your father was right.[\n]To protect that stone[\n]is to protect the world...
Well then, good luck.
Yes.
\[name:R_PC\].
Don't worry, nothing will happen.
......Okay. Because I believe in you.
\[name:R_PC\]!
I'm watching, stay strong!
Don't worry!
\[name:S_PC\].[\n]Please stand on the right side[\n]of the bottom floor.
So let's start the ritual.
Everyone, think of the windy sea[\n]with a calm mind.
\[name:A_PC\], now sing a Rubian Song.
Yes.
What's that...
Is that the original sin?
Also. It's ugly.
Ugh...!!
The form is changing!
Ugh! What's that!
It even transformed!
I don't care if it transformed[\n]or whatever![\n]I'll punish you right now!
Human's original sin[\n]is human's responsibility.[\n]Please defeat original sin.
They have finally appeared.[\n]Their names are[\n]<Wrath>, <Sloth>, <Gluttony>, <Lust>.
The four original sins of human.
Please take charge of it one by one[\n]and defeat it.
Don't worry, I'll beat it down.
It doesn't seem easy, though.
And that doesn't seem too hard,[\n]does it?
Ge...get ready! Monsters are coming![\n]
Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!![\n]Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!!
It seems that everyone has gathered.[\n]Is everyone ready?
Hi?
\[name:R_PC\]Mr. It's been a long time.
You did a good job.
<Ergoth>You will be able to fall asleep comfortably.
Who are you?
It is the .goddess. Of the {Clock Tower}.
Woman... goddess?
Woman... goddess!?
Surprised?
Really... Are you the goddess who created the world?
......Yes.
That... So, are we seeing God now?
......That... I think so.
At... Then I have a question.
What did you think <Ergoth>of giving this to him? 3,000 years ago.
......
「Rubian」Is a gift that is inspired by the passion and love of human beings.
Just like we presented fire to humans a long time ago.
And this was given to the most impartial and honest man of his <Ergoth>time.
But... <Ergoth> Also... He was just a human being true to his feelings.
After all, he too was so caught up in self-interest that he twisted the world like this.
Then... Wasn't it just that the goddess had to come to 「Rubian」 herself?
This would be very easy for the goddess.
Because I gave 「Rubian」<Ergoth>to him, the world was thrown into chaos.
After all, the cause is... Because I was more involved in the human world than I needed to be.
If I were to use the power of the goddess in the world to find 「Rubian」Again, there would be another confusion.
And all this suffering will be borne by human beings.
So, return 「Rubian」Here.
But... Thanks to those of you who are brave and have a pure heart, I think we will be able to overcome this crisis.
Ah, you \[name:S_PC\]!
You're here too!
And \[name:M_PC\]!
\[name:A_PC\]!
Then I'll go back.
Wait a minute. There's still work left.
What's left?  <Ergoth>has already been defeated.
Sure thing... Do I have to wait for someone to bring another piece with me?
Yes, please wait for the other pieces to come together.[\n]
It's okay. Let's wait.
So the reason everyone waited here was for the purification of 「Rubian」?[\n]
Yes.
It's okay. I'm waiting.
\[name:M_PC\]!
You're here.
Oh you are, \[name:R_PC\]!
Hi there~
You are \[name:S_PC\]!
You're here too!
You did a good job.
<Ergoth>...... No, your brother would have had lighter shoulders too.
Okay, so now return 「Rubian」To its original place.
I came out with the {Clock Tower}.
Is it all over now?
Huh?
Then I'll go back to Man {Henesys}.
Wait a minute. There's still work left.
What's left?
Is the reason why everyone is gathered here for the purification of 「Rubian」?[\n]
Yes, that's right.[\n]
It's okay. I'm waiting.
So the reason everyone waited here was for the purification of 「Rubian」?[\n]
Yes.
It seems that everyone has gathered.[\n]Is everyone ready?
Okay!
Yeah, I'm ready.
Yes, I'm ready.
Ok... Okay! I'm in!
<Hatch> and <Rina>.[\n]Please step back for a moment.[\n]
......
I want to help too!
This ritual should be conducted only[\n]with these four of the purest heart.
I know you want to help,[\n]but I can't help it.
......
I see.
Your father was right.[\n]To protect that stone[\n]is to protect the world...
Well then, good luck.
Yes.
\[name:R_PC\].
Don't worry, nothing will happen.
......Okay. Because I believe in you.
\[name:R_PC\]!
I'm watching, stay strong!
Don't worry!
\[name:R_PC\].[\n]Please stand on the left side[\n]of the bottom floor.
Is the reason why everyone is gathered here for the purification of 「Rubian」?[\n]
Yes.
It seems that everyone has gathered.[\n]Is everyone ready?
Okay!
Yeah, I'm ready.
Yes, I'm ready.
Ok... Okay! I'm in!
<Hatch> and <Rina>.[\n]Please step back for a moment.[\n]
......
I want to help too!
This ritual should be conducted only[\n]with these four of the purest heart.
I know you want to help,[\n]but I can't help it.
......
I see.
Your father was right.[\n]To protect that stone[\n]is to protect the world...
Well then, good luck.
Yes.
\[name:R_PC\].
Don't worry, nothing will happen.
......Okay. Because I believe in you.
\[name:R_PC\]!
I'm watching, stay strong!
Don't worry!
\[name:S_PC\]Mr. ...
Yep, you're here too. But what's going on with you?
\[name:R_PC\]Mr. ...
It's been a long time. But why is your look-up?
\[name:A_PC\]...[\n]
I'm back.
So... Is the reason we're all here is[\n]to purify the 「Rubian」?
Yes, that's right.[\n]
It's okay. I'll wait.
So... Is the reason we're all here is[\n]to purify the 「Rubian」?
Yes.
It seems that everyone has gathered.[\n]Is everyone ready?
Okay!
Yeah, I'm ready.
Yes, I'm ready.
Ok... Okay! I'm in!
<Hatch> and <Rina>.[\n]Please step back for a moment.[\n]
......
I want to help too!
This ritual should be conducted only[\n]with these four of the purest heart.
I know you want to help,[\n]but I can't help it.
......
I see.
Your father was right.[\n]To protect that stone[\n]is to protect the world...
Well then, good luck.
Yes.
\[name:R_PC\].
Don't worry, nothing will happen.
......Okay. Because I believe in you.
\[name:R_PC\]!
I'm watching, stay strong!
Don't worry!
Yes...?
You did a good job.
Who, who?
......It is the .goddess. Of the {Clock Tower}.
Goddess...?
Woman... A goddess?
That... Is she really the goddess who created the world?
Yes.
You don't feel good.
Is it because of a friend?
......Yes.
Eventually...... I couldn't protect my friend.
......
Don't be too sad.
Breaking up when they meet, and dying when they are born, is an order that no one with life can avoid.
......Yes.
This is the end of your journey.
So, return 「Rubian」Here.
......Yes.
......
......
Well, I'm going home now.
Wait a minute, \[name:M_PC\].[\n]There's still work left.
What do you mean?
\[name:A_PC\].[\n]Please stand on the left side[\n]of the middle floor.
\[name:M_PC\].[\n]Please stand on the right side[\n]of the middle floor
Okay!
Yes!
Yes.
Yes.
They have finally appeared.[\n]Their names are[\n]<Wrath>, <Sloth>, <Gluttony>, <Lust>.
The four original sins of human.
Please take charge of it one by one[\n]and defeat it.
Don't worry, I'll beat it down.
It doesn't seem easy, though.
And that doesn't seem too hard,[\n]does it?
Ge...get ready! Monsters are coming![\n]
Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!![\n]Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!!
They have finally appeared.[\n]Their names are[\n]<Wrath>, <Sloth>, <Gluttony>, <Lust>.
The four original sins of human.
Please take charge of it one by one[\n]and defeat it.
Don't worry, I'll beat it down.
It doesn't seem easy, though.
And that doesn't seem too hard,[\n]does it?
Ge...get ready! Monsters are coming![\n]
Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!![\n]Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!!
They have finally appeared.[\n]Their names are[\n]<Wrath>, <Sloth>, <Gluttony>, <Lust>.
The four original sins of human.
Please take charge of it one by one[\n]and defeat it.
Don't worry, I'll beat it down.
It doesn't seem easy, though.
And that doesn't seem too hard,[\n]does it?
Ge...get ready! Monsters are coming![\n]
Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!![\n]Hyaat!!! Hyaat!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
AHaaa!!!
So let's start the ritual.
Everyone, think of the windy sea[\n]with a calm mind.
\[name:A_PC\], now sing a Rubian Song.
Yes.
Ugh...!!
What's that...
Is that the original sin?
Also. It's ugly.
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
AHaaa!!!
The form is changing!
Ugh! What's that!
It even transformed!
I don't care if it transformed[\n]or whatever![\n]I'll punish you right now!
Human's original sin[\n]is human's responsibility.[\n]Please defeat original sin.
So let's start the ritual.
Everyone, think of the windy sea[\n]with a calm mind.
\[name:A_PC\], now sing a Rubian Song.
Yes.
Ugh...!!
What's that...
Is that the original sin?
Also. It's ugly.
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
AHaaa!!!
The form is changing!
Ugh! What's that!
It even transformed!
I don't care if it transformed[\n]or whatever![\n]I'll punish you right now!
Human's original sin[\n]is human's responsibility.[\n]Please defeat original sin.
So let's start the ritual.
Everyone, think of the windy sea[\n]with a calm mind.
\[name:A_PC\], now sing a Rubian Song.
Yes.
Ugh...!!
What's that...
Is that the original sin?
Also. It's ugly.
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
\[name:A_PC\]!!!
Haaa!!!
The form is changing!
Ugh! What's that!
It even transformed!
I don't care if it transformed[\n]or whatever![\n]I'll punish you right now!
Human's original sin[\n]is human's responsibility.[\n]Please defeat original sin.
Kyaagh~
\[name:A_PC\], are you okay?
Yes... It seems okay.
That monster!!![\n]It's cowardly attacking suddenly!
I'm gonna have to show the coward[\n]a lesson, right?
Kyaagh~
\[name:A_PC\], are you okay?
Yes... It seems okay.
That monster!!![\n]It's cowardly attacking suddenly!
I'm gonna have to show the coward[\n]a lesson, right?
Kyaagh~
\[name:A_PC\], are you okay?
Yes... It seems okay.
That monster!!![\n]It's cowardly attacking suddenly!
I'm gonna have to show the coward[\n]a lesson, right?
Kyaagh~
\[name:A_PC\], are you okay?
Yes... It seems okay.
That monster!!![\n]It's cowardly attacking suddenly!
I'm gonna have to show the coward[\n]a lesson, right?
Now, our long journey will come[\n]to an end if we put the 「Rubian Piece」[\n]into the clock.
If you put a 「Rubian Piece」 into[\n]the clock, the portal will return[\n]to normal, right?
I'm glad everything seems[\n]to have gone well.
Huh? Were you alive?[\n]I was surprised that you suddenly[\n]disappeared.
When all the pieces of 「Rubian」Come together, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of human beings that he has brought with him.
When all the pieces of 「Rubian」Come together, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of human beings that he has brought with him.
Now that all the 「Rubian」pieces[\n]are gathered,[\n] [\n]I want you to purify the original sin[\n]of the humans that 「Rubian」brought.
Purification?
Purification?
Purification?
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
When all the .Ruins. Come together, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of the human beings that they have brought with them.
When all the .Ruins. Come together, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of the human beings that they have brought with them.
Now that 「Rubian」Has all gathered, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of human beings that he has brought with him.
Purification?
Purification?
Purification?
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
When all the pieces of 「Rubian」Come together, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of human beings that he has brought with him.
Now that all the 「Rubian」pieces[\n]are gathered,[\n] [\n]I want you to purify the original sin[\n]of the humans that 「Rubian」brought.
Purification?
Purification?
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
When all the pieces of 「Rubian」Come together, I hope that 「Rubian」Will purify the original sins of human beings that he has brought with him.
Now that all the 「Rubian」pieces[\n]are gathered,[\n] [\n]I want you to purify the original sin[\n]of the humans that 「Rubian」brought.
Purification...?[\n]What are you talking about?
Purification...?[\n]What are you talking about?
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
Yes.[\n]Rubian now brings four original sins[\n]into the human world.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
If the original sin is not purified,[\n]「Rubian」cannot operate normally.
