Hi, \[name:S_PC\]![\n]Still looking laid-back.
Uh, \[name:S_PC\].[\n]You seem kind of busy?
You know the 『Portal Anomaly』[\n]that happened a few days ago, right?
You seem to be free either~
So until the portal anomaly[\n]is cleared up,[\n]the Maple Union is closed.
That's why there's no requests,[\n]no work arrangements,[\n]and for now, I'm just standing guard
Yeah, I can't stay still[\n]just because I'm free!
This is the Maple Union of {Perion}.[\n]The way you're dressed...[\n]You seem to be adventurous.
Unfortunately,[\n]there are no requests at this time.[\n]It's because of the portal anomaly.
When this situation is resolved,[\n]please stop by again next time.[\n]I'm sorry.
That's right~[\n]There's a reason for this.
Yes. That's right.
Actually, it didn't just happen only[\n]in {Perion},[\n]it happened all over the place.
I see.[\n]Then stay strong!
I'm envious, really...[\n]I'm sick and tired of being free here.
The portal is still[\n]the same as that.[\n]Ugh...
But that doesn't mean[\n]I don't know what to do...
.....[\n]...I'm still busy...
Hi, \[name:S_PC\]!
Yes, hi.
By the way,[\n]didn't you see my grandfather?
Yes, he had something[\n]to deliver somewhere.
I don't see him back yet.
