It's a headstone. What is it written?
Ah, this is... The organization chart of the shrine?
.Sir Substitute<Ergoth>, Sir Superior Fuse<Manute>.... And, do you have a name written on it?
It's the names of people who were here hundreds of years, thousands of years ago. Somehow sad...... It's like a tombstone.[\n]
You wouldn't have thought that thousands of years later the shrine would be like this, would you?
.Sir Substitute<Ergoth>, Sir Superior Fuse<Manute>....[\n]
It seems that only this person <Ergoth>has a higher status than that uncle. Uncle Ghost, is he actually a great person?
.Sir Substitute<Ergoth>, Sir Superior Fuse<Manute>....
......That was the name of the ghost uncle<Manute>, right?
Whew~ Is it finally {Forgotten Temple}?
Yap...!
Hey~~~!!
AAAA
