Oh, no! It fell off.
There is a skeleton on the floor.[\n]Next to it, you see a torn diary.[\n]
『"Where is the exit of this jungle?[\n]I've been wandering here[\n]for a few days already."』
Hey...[\n]Stop making such a ridiculous excuse.
Take a look at MINIMAP and GPS[\n]on the screen below and go up.
Going down like this is just wasting time,
It's like a bad leg, making me slip![\n]
Going down like this is just wasting time,
Take a look at MINIMAP and GPS[\n]on the screen below and go up.
[name:R_PC\], if you go here,[\n]you'll get lost more and more.[\n]Let's go back.
Yeah, we'd better jump over[\n]the place we saw earlier[\n]with 『Flash Jump while Dashing』.
