!!!
What, this!
Week~ Whinger~
Ugh~~~
It's sinking.
Pooh!!
...Immerse yourself in...
Ok. This feeling. <Papulatus>The emotion of is right.
Bull... Pooh!
What... What are these rushing emotions?
...Fear...
Ok. All these emotions are coming from over there.
Whew~ I barely landed properly. Have I become a little disciplined?
Huey~ I fell from a really high place.
Where the heck is this?
This... <Papulatus>The emotion of...?
!!!
This... What is it...?
Countless emotions penetrate the whole body.
......Painful?
......Painful?
.....Solitary?
Is there a place where emotions come from?
The change in emotions is huge...
....Hmm...
By the way... Here's something strange.
I feel like complex emotions are flying all over the place.
!!!
Whew~ I landed safely.
But what about <Hatch>?
<Hatch>!!!!
Don't move!!!
!!!
It was almost a big deal, right!!! As soon as you get out of the portal, you'll be left behind!!!
Is this someone else's feeling...
Can't you go back?
Well, it doesn't matter. I <Rina>had no intention of going back until I found it...
!!!
......Here's a crack in time too......
Maybe <Rina>it's over there...
I think I've come pretty deep... <Rina>You'll probably find it soon.
......Rage...
Pooh!
Whew~ It was dangerous.
Haiku!
Who created this portal in the air!
It came down but... Can't go back?
You like. I'll go to the end.
If so, is it in <Papulatus>the mind of the person?
