Hey. What are you doing here?[\n]
......
Huh?[\n]What's wrong?
You don't seem to have much intention[\n]of doing Mr. <Riness>'s mission.
I'm working hard, too.[\n]Anyone can get lost.
No.[\n]You're not get lost.[\n]There's no will to find a way.
There is a skeleton on the floor.[\n]Next to it, you see a torn diary.
『"I was lost and now I know it,[\n]all the roads in the jungle[\n]seem to lead to one."』
『"I think I am at my limit now.[\n]My eyes are closing little by little."』
Jumping while dashing[\n]allows you to jump further[\n]than jumping while walking.
Press 『\[<\]』 twice quickly and holding it to dash,[\n]and then jump in the middle of it.
Huh?
<Hatch>!
Sheesh! What is it, <Hatch>?[\n]Be stubborn!
Sheesh! What is it, <Hatch>?[\n]Be stubborn!
Do whatever you want![\n]I can do it alone!
Do whatever you want![\n]I can do it alone
But, it's suspicious enough.[\n]He doesn't even look like[\n]a nice person to me.
However, even if \[name:R_PC\] group[\n]is bad, Mr. <Riness>'s action[\n]cannot be called justice.
Okay enough!
You kept talking about[\n]doubting Mr. <Riness> all the time[\n]since came here.
And, it's natural for a person[\n]who doubted like that to not do the job[\n]entrusted to him properly.[\n]
And even if you're right,[\n]Mr. <Riness> recognized our talents.
Besides,[\n]\[name:R_PC\] group was looking[\n]for 「Rubian」because of their debt.
Even with common sense,[\n]you can't hand over[\n]such a powerful stuff to such a person.
You're talking badly about[\n]Mr. <Riness> for no reason!
<Hatch>, what's wrong with you?
Justice? What is justice?[\n]Justice depends on[\n]individual standards!
......Hey!!![\n]You really!!!
But there are general standards!
Looks like my standards[\n]are different from yours?
What! Am I wrong!
I'm going to go to {Sleepywood} alone.[\n]If this continues,[\n]we'll just keep fighting...
From here on,[\n]I'm going to move it separately.
I thought you didn't know I was gone...
What are you talking about?
What you're talking about now?[\n]Working with Mr. <Riness>[\n]is also allowed by Grandpa.
(By the way, <Hatch>.[\n]He's not following me at all.)
(What are you doing over there?)
