 Fire Phoenix's eggs with fire. But
The embers of horsepower are going out. Firewood can't raise it to this temperature, so how do you do it...
Come again!? <Ito>Went <Horntail>there to catch it!? Stupid guy!!
<Ito>Thanks to the embers he brought with him, the firepower was back to its original state.
<Manon>This will keep the eggs warm for the time being.
Thank God... So, you can earn quite a bit of time.
Huh? <Horntail>Seriously?
...You meant to do the same, right?
...I was excited then... In fact, I never thought I could defeat it.
Hahaha! The young blood exploded! Never do it again! You have to look at yourself more objectively!
(Whoa, even though I speak for myself, my ears are tickling, but I was in the days of {Henesys}...)
<Horntail>is strong......
I'll give it a try. Plus, I don't think it's necessarily impossible, but something comes to the feel!
It's a big deal. The embers are going out. If you leave it like this, the eggs will cool down and die...
It was really dangerous before... The bandit showed up and barely lived.
Look at this, the power of fire is completely different, isn't it?
Ah, Maybe you can hatch the eggs this way.
In the meantime, I need to practice a little more! <Horntail>To take it down!
Thanks to this,  able to take care of your eggs again. Thank you very much.
However, on the way, the Archer <Manon>took the Fire breath on my behalf.
Archer of orange hair? And then, I <Ito>think I was with him...
<Ito>Thanks to the embers he brought with him, the firepower returned.
I, at that time, was really impressed with the Archer.
The Archer said it was okay, but... It must have actually been quite painful.
So, in the future, I decided to be as courageous and helpful as an Archer.
